<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Skills><Skill><Owner>Abaddon</Owner><Name>Mist Coil</Name><Description>Abaddon releases a coil of deathly mist that can damage an enemy unit or heal a friendly unit at the cost of some of Abaddon's health.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/abaddon_death_coil_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/60/70/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/stcWsFoEfag?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A mysterious vapor from the Font of Avernus now infuses the breath of Abaddon, who releases it at will.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Abaddon</Owner><Name>Aphotic Shield</Name><Description>Summons dark energies around an ally unit, creating a shield that absorbs a set amount of damage before expiring. When the shield is destroyed it will burst and deal damage equal to the amount it could absorb to an area around it. Removes certain types of negative buffs and stuns on cast.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/abaddon_aphotic_shield_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/105/110/115</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/10/8/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/AUZPOPV0FiU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The powers of the black mist rise to absorb attacks like the black mist absorbs light.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Abaddon</Owner><Name>Curse of Avernus</Name><Description>Abaddon strikes an enemy with chilling curse on each attack, causing all units who attack the slowed enemy to gain increased movement speed, along with faster attack speed, for a limited time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/abaddon_frostmourne_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/83iU74QhxWw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The curse that slows an enemy, speeds an ally.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Abaddon</Owner><Name>Borrowed Time</Name><Description>When activated, all damage dealt to you will heal instead of harm. Most negative buffs will also be removed. If the ability is not on cooldown, it will automatically activate if your health falls below 400.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/abaddon_borrowed_time_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/50/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/9J7CPbAg9dU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The most unnatural of all the gifts of the Font of Avernus, this power defies mortal understanding.  What should hurt, instead heals; and what should kill gives strength anew.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Alchemist</Owner><Name>Acid Spray</Name><Description>Sprays high-pressure acid across a target area. Enemy units who step across the contaminated terrain take damage per second and have their armor reduced.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/alchemist_acid_spray_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 130/140/150/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/MUE1KNbho4Q?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Using traditional Alchemy from the Darkbrew family, Razzil concocts an acid that dissolves even the toughest metals.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Alchemist</Owner><Name>Unstable Concoction</Name><Description>Alchemist brews up an unstable concoction that he can throw at an enemy hero, to stun and deal damage in an area around the explosion. The longer the concoction brews, the more damage it deals and the longer the stun. After 5 seconds, the brew reaches its maximum damage and stun time. However, after 5.5 seconds, the concoction will explode on Alchemist himself if not thrown.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/alchemist_unstable_concoction_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/12jG2U6LH6s?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A silver lining to the failure of turning a mountain into gold, this volatile solution has destructive potential.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Alchemist</Owner><Name>Greevil's Greed</Name><Description>Alchemist synthesizes additional gold from his enemies and bounty runes. With each kill, Alchemist earns base bonus gold and extra bonus gold. If Alchemist kills another unit which yields gold within the next 30 seconds, an additional instance of Extra Bonus Gold is added to the total. Additionally, causes bounty runes to yield 3 times their normal gold.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/alchemist_goblins_greed_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uHDQHquQk6E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While it is not a mountain, Razzil has mastered the conversion of smaller compounds to line his pockets.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Alchemist</Owner><Name>Chemical Rage</Name><Description>Alchemist causes his Ogre to enter a chemically induced rage, reducing base attack cooldown and increasing movement speed and regeneration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/alchemist_chemical_rage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/100/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/7SrgzbFp9Rw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The brew Razzil gave to the Ogre during their prison bust has become a useful potion in the midst of combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Alchemist</Owner><Name>Unstable Concoction Throw</Name><Description>Throw it before it blows up!</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/alchemist_unstable_concoction_throw_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ancient Apparition</Owner><Name>Cold Feet</Name><Description>Places a frozen hex on an enemy unit that deals damage over time, but can be dispelled by moving away from the initial cast point.  If the enemy unit doesn't move outside of the given range, it will be stunned and frozen in place after 4 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ancient_apparition_cold_feet_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/150/150/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13/11/9/7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wq_I0TQFqG8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Kaldr's presence draws those around him into a frozen void, threatening to lock them in an icy prison for eternity.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ancient Apparition</Owner><Name>Ice Vortex</Name><Description>Creates a vortex of icy energy that slows movement speed and increases magic damage done in its range.  Lasts 16 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ancient_apparition_ice_vortex_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZK9v1WLg7lc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Frozen, caustic winds are at the whim of Kaldr, chilling the field of battle.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ancient Apparition</Owner><Name>Chilling Touch</Name><Description>A frigid gust enchants allied heroes, granting them bonus magical damage for a given number of physical attacks, while slowing their attack speed slightly.  Ancient Apparition always receives the buff. Lasts 30 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ancient_apparition_chilling_touch_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50/42/34/26</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vmYw33RAlCE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Ancient Apparition's eternal knowledge brings a frigid enchantment to his allies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ancient Apparition</Owner><Name>Ice Blast</Name><Description>Launches a tracer toward any location on the battlefield, which must be triggered again to mark the area to be blasted by a damaging explosion of hail. The further the tracer travels, the larger the explosion will be. Enemies caught in the explosion, or who touch the icy ball of hail as it travels, are Frostbitten, taking damage and prevented from regenerating or healing. If a Frostbitten unit's health drops below a certain percentage, they will instantly shatter.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ancient_apparition_ice_blast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/125/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/j97qGajoj1s?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ice storms from ages past flow through Kaldr's frosty limbs, crashing into the world and turning its inhabitants into monuments to his eternal power.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ancient Apparition</Owner><Name>Release</Name><Description>Releases the ice blast to explode at the tracer's current location.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ancient_apparition_ice_blast_release_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Anti-Mage</Owner><Name>Mana Break</Name><Description>Burns an opponent's mana on each attack.  Mana Break deals 60% of the mana burned as damage to the target.

Mana Break is a Unique Attack Modifier, and does not stack with other Unique Attack Modifiers.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/antimage_mana_break_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5n9dPC349Lw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A modified technique of the Turstarkuri monks' peaceful ways is to turn magical energies on their owner.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Anti-Mage</Owner><Name>Blink</Name><Description>Short distance teleportation that allows Anti-Mage to move in and out of combat.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/antimage_blink_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/60/60/60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/9/7/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HCJe7ilCyXo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In his encounter with the Dead Gods, Anti-Mage learned the value of being elusive.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Anti-Mage</Owner><Name>Spell Shield</Name><Description>Increases Anti-Mage's resistance to magic damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/antimage_spell_shield_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/pQ6OlMLiA-A?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Years of meditation and obsession with revenge have hardened Anti-Mage's skin against mystical opponents.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Anti-Mage</Owner><Name>Mana Void</Name><Description>For each point of mana missing by the target unit, damage is dealt to it and surrounding enemies.  The main target is also mini-stunned.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/antimage_mana_void_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/200/275</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/qi1_xFE6nBI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>After bringing enemies to their knees, Anti-Mage punishes them for their use of the arcane arts.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Arc Warden</Owner><Name>Flux</Name><Description>Infuses a lone enemy unit with swirling, volatile energy, slowing its movement speed and dealing damage over time. The effect is muted if another enemy unit is near the target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/arc_warden_flux_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 18</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>An infinitesimal fraction of the power which imprisoned the Ancients.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Arc Warden</Owner><Name>Magnetic Field</Name><Description>Generates a circular distortion field of magnetic energy that protects allied heroes and buildings within it by evading attacks coming from outside the field.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/arc_warden_magnetic_field_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35/30/25/20</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Time and space are of little consequence to one as old as Zet.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Arc Warden</Owner><Name>Spark Wraith</Name><Description>Summons a Spark Wraith that slowly materializes and patrols a targeted area until an enemy comes within its range. Once a target has been found the wraith fuses with them, dealing magical damage and purging the unit.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/arc_warden_spark_wraith_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Lesser fragments of Zet's original self.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Arc Warden</Owner><Name>Tempest Double</Name><Description>Briefly refocusing its fractured elements into a single form, the Arc Warden is able to create a perfect electrical duplication of itself. The duplicate can use all of Arc Warden's current items and spells, except items that drop on death. The duplicate has seperate item and ability cooldowns.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/arc_warden_tempest_double_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40/35/30</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Warped by the power of its peers, Arc Warden becomes what it despises most: disharmony.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Axe</Owner><Name>Berserker's Call</Name><Description>Axe taunts nearby enemy units, forcing them to attack him, while he gains bonus armor during the duration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/axe_berserkers_call_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/14/12/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/EYSMC12J9vw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Mogul Khan's warcry taunts opponents into engaging in an unconquerable battle with the Axe.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Axe</Owner><Name>Battle Hunger</Name><Description>Enrages an enemy unit, causing it to be slowed and take damage over time until it kills another unit or the duration ends. Axe gains movement speed for each unit affected with Battle Hunger.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/axe_battle_hunger_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/15/10/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1Xmzu79iaX0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ordinary heroes cannot withstand Mogul Khan's rage for battle, such that it injures them until it is satisfied.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Axe</Owner><Name>Counter Helix</Name><Description>When attacked, Axe performs a helix counter attack, dealing pure damage to all nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/axe_counter_helix_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0.45/0.40/0.35/0.30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vSvMgF_gAqo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Axe is the only reinforcement this army needs.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Axe</Owner><Name>Culling Blade</Name><Description>Axe spots a weakness and strikes, instantly killing an enemy unit with low health, or dealing moderate damage otherwise. When an enemy hero is killed with Culling Blade, its cooldown is reset, and Axe and nearby allied units gain bonus movement speed.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/axe_culling_blade_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/120/180</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 75/65/55</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/iSkNp5ty7xI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Mogul Khan is the embodiment of battle and fury, launching into a gruesome fatality against those who dare engage the Axe in combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bane</Owner><Name>Enfeeble</Name><Description>Weakens an enemy unit, reducing its physical damage.  Lasts 20 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bane_enfeeble_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cSZQr6qFcnQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Even the mightiest of warriors crumble before the terror of Atropos.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bane</Owner><Name>Brain Sap</Name><Description>Feasts on the vital energies of an enemy unit, healing Bane and dealing damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bane_brain_sap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/100/130/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/13/12/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/aO14tLgQXVo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Atropos finds no greater pleasure than to harvest the fear he creates.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bane</Owner><Name>Nightmare</Name><Description>Puts the target enemy or friendly Hero to sleep and deals damage per second.  Sleeping units are awakened when attacked, but the Nightmare passes to the attacking unit.  The nightmared unit instantly wakes up if it takes damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bane_nightmare_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 165/165/165/165</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/19/16/13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FExnzA0Pes4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A stolen prowess from the goddess Nyctasha is to put his prey into forever sleep.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bane</Owner><Name>Fiend's Grip</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Grips an enemy unit, disabling it and causing heavy damage over time, while stealing mana every second based on the unit's maximum mana.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bane_fiends_grip_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/300/400</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/GFDyNOUnLFw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Victims of Atropos are frequently torn apart by vivid conjurations of their own nightmares.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bane</Owner><Name>Nightmare End</Name><Description>Ends all ongoing Nightmares.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bane_nightmare_end_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Batrider</Owner><Name>Sticky Napalm</Name><Description>Drenches an area in sticky oil, amplifying damage from Batrider's attacks and abilities and slowing the movement speed and turn rate of enemies in the area.  Additional casts of Sticky Napalm continue to increase damage, up to 10 stacks.  The extra damage is halved against creeps.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/batrider_sticky_napalm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 20/20/20/20</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 3</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jru8juajIig?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It's not uncommon to hear the Rider cackle while he increases the flammability of his opponents.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Batrider</Owner><Name>Flamebreak</Name><Description>Hurls an explosive cocktail that explodes when it reaches the target location, knocking back, briefly stunning, and dealing damage over time to enemies in the area.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/batrider_flamebreak_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uQuU3UPz4lE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A molotov cocktail is the weapon of choice for Batrider.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Batrider</Owner><Name>Firefly</Name><Description>Batrider takes to the skies, laying down a trail of flames from the air.  The fire damages any enemies it touches, and destroys trees below Batrider. While flying, Batrider gains unobstructed movement and vision.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/batrider_firefly_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/X4vRNtSfFwE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When an enemy escapes into the Yama Raskav Jungle, most would cut through the brush to find the fugitive.  Batrider just chooses to destroy the jungle along with his foes.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Batrider</Owner><Name>Flaming Lasso</Name><Description>Lassoes an enemy and drags them in Batrider's wake.  Victims cannot be dragged over impassable terrain. Dragged units cannot move, attack, or use abilities.  Teleporting or blinking will break the lasso.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/batrider_flaming_lasso_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 225</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90/75/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Fem29nDrc04?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Few dare to ask to ride on the bat, as Batrider gives them free of charge.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Beastmaster</Owner><Name>Wild Axes</Name><Description>Beastmaster sends his axes flying and calls them home again, slicing through enemy units and trees along their path.  Each axe can hit an enemy once.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/beastmaster_wild_axes_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RfMTKPalQ_E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While learning to maneuver in nature alone, the Beastmaster also mastered the use of a pair of tomahawks, adept at cutting down trees as well as adversaries.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Beastmaster</Owner><Name>Call of the Wild: Hawk</Name><Description>Beastmaster calls forth a watchful Hawk to scout the battlefield. At level 3 and beyond, the hawk can become invisible after being still for 4 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/beastmaster_call_of_the_wild_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 42/38/34/30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/az1QugljYAA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>After befriending the strange beast of his childhood, Beastmaster has learned to call to animals in times of need.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Beastmaster</Owner><Name>Inner Beast</Name><Description>Untaps the inner fury of allies, passively increasing their attack speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/beastmaster_inner_beast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/aC2jU2vrI8U?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Beastmaster's ability to incite the innate strength of animals was seen in the mauling of the king of Slom.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Beastmaster</Owner><Name>Primal Roar</Name><Description>Beastmaster lets loose a deafening roar that stuns, and shoves open, a path to its target. All units in the path of the roar are damaged, while units shoved aside by the roar have their movement and attack speed slowed.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/beastmaster_primal_roar_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/175/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80/75/70</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/mnHbT9GLIdU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Beastmaster has learned to channel his primal instincts into an animalistic roar, causing devastation in the ranks of enemies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bloodseeker</Owner><Name>Bloodrage</Name><Description>Drives a unit into a bloodthirsty rage during which a unit deals, and takes, increased damage. Units affected by Bloodrage will be healed for a percentage of the max health of any units they kill. Units affected by Bloodrage when killed will heal a percentage of their max health to their killer.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bloodseeker_bloodrage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/10/8/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BnTDtOHIatY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Strygwyr shares his animalistic thirst for bloodshed.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bloodseeker</Owner><Name>Blood Rite</Name><Description>Bloodseeker baptizes an area in sacred blood. After 3 seconds the ritual completes, causing any enemies caught in the area to take damage and become silenced.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bloodseeker_blood_bath_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25/21/17/13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/z2PQgLOoDZE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Flayed Twins are ever willing to aid those who spill blood upon the field of battle.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bloodseeker</Owner><Name>Thirst</Name><Description>Bloodseeker is invigorated by the wounds of his enemies, gaining bonus movement speed and attack damage whenever an enemy hero's health falls below 75%, with the bonuses increasing as their health falls further. If an enemy hero's health falls below 25%, he will also gain vision and True Sight of that hero. Bonuses stack per hero.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bloodseeker_thirst_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/VcJPbm7kek8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Strygwyr becomes frenzied when blood is spilled.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bloodseeker</Owner><Name>Rupture</Name><Description>Causes an enemy unit's skin to rupture. If the unit moves, it takes a percentage of the distance traveled as damage.  The damage is dealt through spell immunity.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bloodseeker_rupture_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/200/250</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gf8HgbLF-7Y?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When the Bloodseeker hunts you, injuries become fatalities.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bounty Hunter</Owner><Name>Shuriken Toss</Name><Description>Hurls a deadly shuriken at an enemy unit, dealing damage and mini-stunning the target.  The shuriken will bounce between any Tracked units who are within a 1200 radius of each other.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bounty_hunter_shuriken_toss_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/130/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/THFY7EAD7HY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While the shuriken may be small, Gondar's precise aim can cause critical damage.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bounty Hunter</Owner><Name>Jinada</Name><Description>Bounty Hunter plans his next hit, passively adding a critical strike and maim to his next attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bounty_hunter_jinada_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/10/8/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/JVqW1Gyi5FM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Whispering an enchantment he learned from Soruq to his faithful blades, Gondar targets vital tendons and joints to disable his opponents.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bounty Hunter</Owner><Name>Shadow Walk</Name><Description>Bounty Hunter becomes invisible and gains the ability to move through other units until he attacks or uses an ability.  If he breaks the invisibility with an attack, that attack will deal bonus damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bounty_hunter_wind_walk_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 65</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/A1pTdYaSDo0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The court jesters present during King Goff's assassination can recount no other image than a dancing shadow.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bounty Hunter</Owner><Name>Track</Name><Description>Tracks an enemy hero, granting True Sight of the target, and information on how much gold it is carrying. Allies near the hunted are granted bonus movement speed. If the target dies, Bounty Hunter and nearby heroes collect a bonus bounty of gold.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bounty_hunter_track_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/QUR30zbpNDs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Using his elevated senses of sight and smell, Gondar's hits have quite a good chance of success.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Brewmaster</Owner><Name>Thunder Clap</Name><Description>Slams the ground, dealing damage and slowing the movement speed and attack rate of nearby enemy land units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/brewmaster_thunder_clap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/105/130/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/iff_66q_-WI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A slam of Mangix' mighty keg starts the festivities.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Brewmaster</Owner><Name>Drunken Haze</Name><Description>Drenches a small area in alcohol, causing their movement speed to be reduced, and causing their attacks to have a chance to miss.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/brewmaster_drunken_haze_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8/7/6/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/o5T4GnOGj5o?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Order of the Oyo's solution to all problems - another round!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Brewmaster</Owner><Name>Drunken Brawler</Name><Description>Gives a chance to avoid attacks and to deal critical damage. Drunken Brawler will always trigger if you have not attacked, or have not been attacked, in the last several seconds.

Stacks diminishingly with other sources of Evasion.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/brewmaster_drunken_brawler_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/mYA6AFcxVhk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When Mangix won his title as the Brewmaster of the Order of Oyo, he also claimed his place in the mastery of inebriation.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Brewmaster</Owner><Name>Primal Split</Name><Description>Splits Brewmaster into elements, forming 3 specialized warriors, adept at survival. If any of them survive until the end of their summoned timer, the Brewmaster is reborn.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/brewmaster_primal_split_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/150/175</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140/120/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uLqYQIf9OuE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It isn't clear whether Mangix is consciously aware of his potent bond with nature, as it often occurs in the midst of a drunken stupor.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bristleback</Owner><Name>Viscous Nasal Goo</Name><Description>Covers a target in snot, causing it to have reduced armor and movement speed.  Multiple casts stack and refresh the duration.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bristleback_viscous_nasal_goo_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/hYjBnO7iwj4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Having caught a cold while stuck in the snow, Bristleback turns it to his advantage.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bristleback</Owner><Name>Quill Spray</Name><Description>Sprays enemy units with quills dealing damage in an area of effect around Bristleback.  Deals bonus damage for every time a unit was hit by Quill Spray in the last 14 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bristleback_quill_spray_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 35/35/35/35</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 3</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/9GopSwJPPO8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An enforcer's honor can be a prickly thing.  So can his quills.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bristleback</Owner><Name>Bristleback</Name><Description>Bristleback takes less damage if hit on the sides or rear.  If Bristleback takes 210 damage from the rear, he releases a Quill Spray of the current level.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bristleback_bristleback_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/0peFZ-iqxRA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Turning his back to a fight might be just the thing.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Bristleback</Owner><Name>Warpath</Name><Description>Bristleback works himself up into a fury every time he casts a spell, increasing his movement speed and damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/bristleback_warpath_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IQsYSrW9-QI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>'Temper, temper,' his mum always chided.  But in a fight, a temper can come in handy.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Broodmother</Owner><Name>Spawn Spiderlings</Name><Description>Broodmother injects her young into an enemy unit, dealing damage. The spiderlings will hatch if the target is killed while under this influence.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/broodmother_spawn_spiderlings_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HsrNXKf_QOY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Black Arachnia continues to raise her young, even amidst the field of combat.  The brood quickly learns how to support their mother.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Broodmother</Owner><Name>Spin Web</Name><Description>Spins a large web that renders Broodmother invisible, grants a passive movement speed increase, gives free movement, and boosts regeneration while in its vicinity. Spin Web charges restore every 40 seconds. If damage is taken, free movement is disabled and the movement speed increase is halved for 6 seconds. Spin Web can be cast from anywhere as long as the new web touches an existing web. Webs never expire, and can be manually destroyed. When the maximum limit of webs is exceeded, the oldest web disappears.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/broodmother_spin_web_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/rTMrFJkcWTk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Weaving a bed of silken fibers, Arachnia's web both protects her and her offspring, as well as giving advancing opponents a sense of forboding.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Broodmother</Owner><Name>Incapacitating Bite</Name><Description>Broodmother's venom cripples enemy units, causing her attacks to slow and giving the affected unit a chance to miss its attacks.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/broodmother_incapacitating_bite_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fewADuqpwLM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Paralytic toxins come from Black Arachnia's fangs, causing a slow and painful death to those who intrude on her webs.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Broodmother</Owner><Name>Insatiable Hunger</Name><Description>A violent lust for vital fluids increases Broodmother's attack damage and gives her a vampiric attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/broodmother_insatiable_hunger_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/zxPfDpll2II?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While most of her prey is wrapped in silken cocoons and saved for her young, the Broodmother herself has a taste for wandering heroes.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Centaur Warrunner</Owner><Name>Hoof Stomp</Name><Description>Slams the ground, stunning and damaging nearby enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/centaur_hoof_stomp_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FuWaTlMJwjM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When the mighty hoof of the Warrunner touches soil, the tremors are felt far and wide.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Centaur Warrunner</Owner><Name>Double Edge</Name><Description>Centaur strikes a mighty blow at melee range, damaging both himself and a small area around the target.  Centaur cannot die from Double Edge.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/centaur_double_edge_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/PsHWOHEq5-Q?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the spurs of combat, Bradwarden's vicious strikes sometimes cause self-inflicted collateral damage.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Centaur Warrunner</Owner><Name>Return</Name><Description>Centaur counters every attack, damaging the attacker based on a percentage of Centaur's strength.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/centaur_return_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/b0obuqv_n5I?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Bradwarden has no need to parry his opponent's attacks; his armor-like hide does it for him.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Centaur Warrunner</Owner><Name>Stampede</Name><Description>Centaur leads all allies into a vicious charge causing them to move through units at max speed and stop any enemy units they trample. Trampled enemies take damage based on Centaur Warrunner's strength. Each enemy can be trampled once.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/centaur_stampede_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90/75/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RF6R96LLL5o?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The great belt of Omexe, which labels Bradwarden as the greatest warrior of his kind, incites his fellow gladiators to follow him into barbarous combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chaos Knight</Owner><Name>Chaos Bolt</Name><Description>Throws a mysterious bolt of energy at the target unit. It stuns for a random duration and deals random damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chaos_knight_chaos_bolt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 140/140/140/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/O0qGKxIvJgw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Even Chaos Knight cannot predict this manifest of unholy energy.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chaos Knight</Owner><Name>Reality Rift</Name><Description>Teleports you, any images you have and the target unit to a random point along the line between the two of you. Gives you bonus attack damage for one attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chaos_knight_reality_rift_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24/18/12/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5aT3Q78qtzQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Armageddon rides between the planes, bringing Chaos Knight to his victim wherever he may hide.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chaos Knight</Owner><Name>Chaos Strike</Name><Description>Each of Chaos Knight's attacks has a chance to deal bonus damage and reduce the target's armor by 5 for 8 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chaos_knight_chaos_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Oi8uwcdvz_s?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Chaos Knight's unwieldy power bludgeons those who stand before him, crushing the thickest of armors.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chaos Knight</Owner><Name>Phantasm</Name><Description>Summons several phantasmal copies of the Chaos Knight from alternate dimensions. There is a 50% chance an extra phantasm will be summoned. The phantasms deal full damage, but take double damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chaos_knight_phantasm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/200/275</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 130</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/P-DaVdeSUiI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Drawing on his battles fought across many worlds and many times, phantasms of the Chaos Knight rise up to quell all who oppose him.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chen</Owner><Name>Penitence</Name><Description>Forces an enemy unit to move slower and take more damage from attacks and spells.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chen_penitence_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/13/12/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Q0lQaxZ2bG8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Although Chen's brand of animal enthrallment isn't quite strong enough to control the minds of enemy heroes, it still tests their resolve in combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chen</Owner><Name>Test of Faith</Name><Description>Deals random damage to test an enemy unit's faith.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chen_test_of_faith_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/NfeyK2IK4mg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Knights of the Fold possess a fanatical form of magic that is considered quite unwieldy by most other users of arcane arts.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chen</Owner><Name>Test of Faith</Name><Description>Teleports an allied unit back to the base.  Creeps are teleported instantly, while Heroes have a delay before teleporting. If cast on Chen, all units controlled by Chen through Holy Persuasion will be teleported to him after a delay.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chen_test_of_faith_teleport_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/200/200/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/TY-WEAij0KM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chen</Owner><Name>Holy Persuasion</Name><Description>Chen takes control of an enemy or neutral creep. If the persuaded creep's base health is naturally below the health minimum, its base health will be raised to the health minimum.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter, allowing Chen to persuade Ancient Creeps. The number of Ancient Creeps that can be persuaded is based on the level of Hand of God.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chen_holy_persuasion_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/26/22/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Jhk_gA5AeZo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Although they may not be knights, Chen incorporates beasts into the Fold in the same way he himself was converted.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Chen</Owner><Name>Hand of God</Name><Description>Heals all allied heroes on the map as well as all units under Chen's control.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/chen_hand_of_god_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/300/400</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 160/140/120</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BxXGyInKTpQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Using the mental link with his thralls, Chen calls down restoration and well-being to those who share his fanaticism.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clinkz</Owner><Name>Strafe</Name><Description>Clinkz attacks with a barrage of arrows.  Dramatically increases attack speed for a short time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/clinkz_strafe_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/90/90/90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40/35/30/25</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/6ZXx_EB7RqA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It's hard to say whether the blur around the Bone Fletcher is from his flaming heart or his speed with the quiver.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clinkz</Owner><Name>Searing Arrows</Name><Description>Imbues Clinkz's arrows with fire for extra damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/clinkz_searing_arrows_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 10</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jYysnmhcZ7Y?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Clinkz simply lights his arrows from his flaming essence for quite the destructive effect.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clinkz</Owner><Name>Skeleton Walk</Name><Description>Clinkz moves invisibly through units until the moment he attacks or uses an ability.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/clinkz_wind_walk_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/19/18/17</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/zr56m_VHdCU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With a burst of fire and puff of smoke, the Bone Fletcher was nowhere to be seen.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clinkz</Owner><Name>Death Pact</Name><Description>Clinkz consumes the target friendly or enemy creep, gaining a percent of its hitpoints as max health and damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/clinkz_death_pact_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45/35/25</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fS5fKvleNro?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Sutherex' bond of life and death has become a part of Clinkz, and his old bones are refreshed with repetition of the pact on lesser beings.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clockwerk</Owner><Name>Battery Assault</Name><Description>Discharges high-powered shrapnel at random nearby enemy units, dealing minor magical damage and ministun.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rattletrap_battery_assault_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 32/28/24/20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5P3Dk2VzVVo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Some of Rattletrap's contraptions don't quite work correctly, so detonating them proves useful as an offensive maneuver.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clockwerk</Owner><Name>Power Cogs</Name><Description>Forms a barrier of energized cogs around Clockwerk, trapping any units that are near.  Enemies outside the trap that touch a cog are knocked back, losing health and mana. Once a cog has delivered a shock, it will power down.  Cogs can be destroyed by enemy attacks, but Clockwerk can destroy them with just one.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rattletrap_power_cogs_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/60/70/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/rzTnmYGoJXA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>One of Clockwerk's inventions of which he is most proud is the power cog - though it is sometimes despised by his allies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clockwerk</Owner><Name>Rocket Flare</Name><Description>Fires a global range flare that explodes over a given area, damaging enemies and providing vision for 10 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rattletrap_rocket_flare_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/18/16/14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/etHgBKQTjEE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>What started as a festive display has become a useful scouting and bombardment tool.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Clockwerk</Owner><Name>Hookshot</Name><Description>Fires a grappling device rapidly at the target location.  If the hook hits a unit, Clockwerk launches himself into the target, stunning and dealing damage.  Any enemies Clockwerk collides with along the way are damaged and stunned.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rattletrap_hookshot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/150/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70/55/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fbAceDpaO2s?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A somewhat unwieldy device, the Hookshot sends the otherwise clunky Clockwerk armor flying through the air.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Crystal Maiden</Owner><Name>Crystal Nova</Name><Description>A burst of damaging frost slows enemy movement and attack rate in the targeted area.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/crystal_maiden_crystal_nova_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/120/140/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/11/10/9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/hv-wIna71VQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The air temperature around Rylai drops rapidly, chilling all around her to the core.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Crystal Maiden</Owner><Name>Frostbite</Name><Description>Encases an enemy unit in ice, prohibiting movement and attack, while dealing 50 damage every half-second. Lasts 10 seconds on creeps level 6 or lower.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/crystal_maiden_frostbite_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 115/125/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 9/8/7/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/6FnrLNZxtxQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Rylai channels winds from the Blueheart Glacier, imprisoning attackers in thick blocks of ice.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Crystal Maiden</Owner><Name>Arcane Aura</Name><Description>Gives additional mana regeneration to all friendly units on the map. This bonus is increased for Crystal Maiden.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/crystal_maiden_brilliance_aura_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/JGBd1B3UW38?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Cold temperatures promote the essence of magic, causing Rylai's presence to allow spell usage in abundance.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Crystal Maiden</Owner><Name>Freezing Field</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Surrounds Crystal Maiden with random icy explosions that slow enemies and deal massive damage.  Lasts 10 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/crystal_maiden_freezing_field_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/400/600</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/xesyW_27uJc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Once the place of her exile, Icewrack has become an anchor for Rylai's frigid onslaught.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dark Seer</Owner><Name>Vacuum</Name><Description>Dark Seer creates a vacuum over the target area that sucks in enemy units, disrupting them and dealing damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dark_seer_vacuum_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/130/160/190</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 28</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/X9BW1-PhEY8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ish'Kafel modifies the center of gravity to a place of his choosing.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dark Seer</Owner><Name>Ion Shell</Name><Description>Surrounds the target unit with a bristling shield that damages enemy units in an area around it.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dark_seer_ion_shell_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/90/110/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZnXjN2FdNQA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Dark Seer slices holes into the 'Land Behind the Wall,' causing prismatic energy to seep forth.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dark Seer</Owner><Name>Surge</Name><Description>Charges a target friendly unit with power, giving it a brief burst of maximum movement speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dark_seer_surge_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/11/10/9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Vi9f-Bs2KX0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ish'Kafel once used his speed of mind to navigate the maze between the walls.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dark Seer</Owner><Name>Wall of Replica</Name><Description>Raises a wall of warping light that damages and creates replicas of any enemy hero who crosses it. Enemy replicas serve at the Dark Seer's will. Replicas last until they are destroyed, or until the wall's duration ends.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dark_seer_wall_of_replica_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/250/375</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/3Z1ndpKQZVg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Dark Seer, while unable to return to his natural realm, can channel part of the prismatic wall with powerful strength of mind, sowing confusion amongst enemy ranks.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dazzle</Owner><Name>Poison Touch</Name><Description>Casts a poisonous spell on an enemy unit, gradually slowing movement, and causing damage over time.
LEVEL 1 - Slows the target by 33% for 3 seconds.
LEVEL 2 - Slows the target by 33% for 2 seconds, then by 66% for 1 second.
LEVEL 3 - Slows the target by 33%, 66%, and 100%, for 1 second each.
LEVEL 4 - Slows the target by 33% for 1 second, then 66% for 1 second, then stuns for 1 second.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dazzle_poison_touch_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15/13/11/7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/iNu7gMUOovI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>One of the few Dezun rites used for offensive purposes, the paralytic enchantment often proves useful.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dazzle</Owner><Name>Shallow Grave</Name><Description>An ally blessed with Shallow Grave, no matter how close to death, cannot die while under its protection.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dazzle_shallow_grave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/45/30/15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/iW-w1R0pcZI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Only a seasoned acolyte of the Shadow can properly perform the rite of preventing death.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dazzle</Owner><Name>Shadow Wave</Name><Description>Sends out a bolt of power that arcs between allies, healing them while damaging any units standing nearby.  Dazzle is always healed by Shadow Wave.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dazzle_shadow_wave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/10/8/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/hiqYtx3MNck?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While it is a simplistic and routine rite among Shadow Priests, the Shadow Wave is also the most critical for success.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dazzle</Owner><Name>Weave</Name><Description>Applies a buff that increases the armor of allied heroes while decreasing the armor of enemy heroes in the target area over time.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dazzle_weave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/kobWMCcOQLc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>His ethereal journey into the Nothl realm has allowed Dazzle to mend together the powers of light and dark, creating shifting waves of enchantments.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Death Prophet</Owner><Name>Crypt Swarm</Name><Description>Sends a swarm of winged beasts to savage enemy units in front of Death Prophet.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/death_prophet_carrion_swarm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 105/120/140/165</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8/7/6/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/z_uGWWazyqg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Krobelus' many trips to the grave gather a flock of the damned.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Death Prophet</Owner><Name>Silence</Name><Description>Prevents enemy units in a target area from casting spells.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/death_prophet_silence_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/80/80/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15/14/13/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/eLBBXHVFYgU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Peering into the veil of her opponent's demise, Krobelus sees a silent future.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Death Prophet</Owner><Name>Spirit Siphon</Name><Description>Creates a spirit link between Death Prophet and an enemy unit, draining 14 + 1% Max HP per second and slowing the enemy's movement speed by 5%.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/death_prophet_spirit_siphon_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/65/60/55</Mana><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Death Prophet</Owner><Name>Exorcism</Name><Description>Unleashes evil spirits to drain the life of nearby enemy units and structures. At the end of the spell's duration, Death Prophet is healed in proportion to the damage dealt.  Lasts 35 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/death_prophet_exorcism_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/300/400</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 145</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/UpxNoiCXx1g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Over time, the banshee remnants of her previous lives return to haunt the present.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Disruptor</Owner><Name>Thunder Strike</Name><Description>Repeatedly strikes the targeted unit with lightning.  Each strike damages nearby enemy units in a small radius.  Provides vision of its target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/disruptor_thunder_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 130/130/130/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/11/10/9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cgsZb1yUxAE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Disruptor's charged coils occasionally overload, and a singed armor plate or tuft of fur is the enemy's result.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Disruptor</Owner><Name>Glimpse</Name><Description>Teleports the target hero back to where it was 4 seconds ago.  Instantly kills illusions.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/disruptor_glimpse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/46/32/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/npnjwS7jIco?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Playing with electricity can have unexpected results.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Disruptor</Owner><Name>Kinetic Field</Name><Description>After a short formation time, creates a circular barrier of kinetic energy that enemies can't pass.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/disruptor_kinetic_field_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/70/70/70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13/12/11/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/T8vTW3QdEEc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The stryder is immune to the gale-force winds that will consume its adversaries.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Disruptor</Owner><Name>Static Storm</Name><Description>Creates a damaging static storm that also silences all enemy units in the area for the duration.  The damage starts off weak, but increases in power over the duration.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/disruptor_static_storm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/175/225</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90/80/70</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5a6DMRqF2o8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A summer squall in Druud is a hardship that only an Oglodi can survive.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Doom</Owner><Name>Devour</Name><Description>Consumes an enemy or neutral creep, acquiring any special abilities that it possessed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/doom_bringer_devour_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70/60/50/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/hbJpllULcxo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lucifer's appetite and greed are never sated.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Doom</Owner><Name>Scorched Earth</Name><Description>Carpets the nearby earth in flames which damage enemies and heal Doom, while also granting him increased movement speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/doom_bringer_scorched_earth_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/65/70/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 55</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Cma29C2JmqM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Fallen One spreads destruction in his wake, sparing none from the flame which sustains him.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Doom</Owner><Name>Infernal Blade</Name><Description>Doom swings his burning sword, igniting the enemy. Stuns for 0.3 seconds and applies a 4 second burn that deals 25 + 1.25% of the target's Max HP as damage per second.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/doom_bringer_infernal_blade_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/12/8/4</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Lucifer shares the fire branding bestowed upon him at the time of his exile.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Doom</Owner><Name>Doom</Name><Description>Inflicts a curse that prevents an enemy Hero from casting spells or using items, while taking damage over time.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/doom_bringer_doom_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/200/250</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 145</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/6fFIUnuh1r0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When a name is tolled from the bell of Vashundol, doom is sure to follow.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dragon Knight</Owner><Name>Breathe Fire</Name><Description>Unleashes a breath of fire in front of Dragon Knight that burns enemies and reduces the damage their attacks deal.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dragon_knight_breathe_fire_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/110/120/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/13/12/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wrZnzBN1CmA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Knight Davion's breath has become that of the mighty Eldwurm Slyrak, remembered for burning numerous other knights to a crisp.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dragon Knight</Owner><Name>Dragon Tail</Name><Description>Dragon Knight smites an enemy unit in melee range with his shield, stunning it while dealing minor damage.  When in Elder Dragon Form, the cast range increases to 400.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dragon_knight_dragon_tail_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/11/10/9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gJSc04KMmbE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Davion's combination of dragon talents and knightly skills makes him a vicious opponent in melee combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dragon Knight</Owner><Name>Dragon Blood</Name><Description>The life blood of the Dragon improves health regeneration and strengthens armor.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dragon_knight_dragon_blood_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/mbzF8oyAUfc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Slyrak's blood still courses through Davion's veins, giving him twice the vitality of an ordinary knight.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Dragon Knight</Owner><Name>Elder Dragon Form</Name><Description>Dragon Knight takes the form of one of three powerful elder dragons, increasing his speed, and Dragon Tail's range, while granting him new powers.
LEVEL 1 Green Dragon - Corrosive Breath: attacks deal 20 poison damage per second for 5 seconds. Works on structures.
LEVEL 2 Red Dragon - Splash Attack: attacks damage all enemy units in a 300 radius, with Corrosive Breath added to the primary target.
LEVEL 3 Blue Dragon - Frost Breath: slows movement speed by 30% and attack speed by 20 of enemy units in Splash Attack range for 3 seconds, with Corrosive Breath added to the primary target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/dragon_knight_elder_dragon_form_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 115</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/3HpgABQ8kpA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The dormant dragon power springs forth from within Davion, combining the powers of a legendary knight with a legendary Eldwurm.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Drow Ranger</Owner><Name>Frost Arrows</Name><Description>Adds a freezing effect to Drow's attacks, slowing enemy movement.  Lasts 1.5 seconds on Heroes, and 7 seconds on creeps.

Frost Arrows is a Unique Attack Modifier, and does not stack with other Unique Attack Modifiers.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/drow_ranger_frost_arrows_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 12/12/12/12</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/u6dvUwbjI_k?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ice-encased arrows pierce the silence, chilling their victims to the core.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Drow Ranger</Owner><Name>Gust</Name><Description>Releases a wave that silences and knocks back enemy units. Knockback distance is relative to how close they are to you.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/drow_ranger_wave_of_silence_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Traxex is rather fond of the tranquility of physical combat, calling on her Drow heritage to end the incantations of opposing magi.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Drow Ranger</Owner><Name>Precision Aura</Name><Description>Adds bonus damage to the physical attack of allied, ranged Hero units based on a percentage of Drow's agility.  Affects creeps for 30 seconds when cast.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/drow_ranger_trueshot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wNzhcuzDmf0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Traxex' time spent alone in the forests of her Drow home has allowed her to teach other archers how to improve their bow skills.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Drow Ranger</Owner><Name>Marksmanship</Name><Description>Drow's experiences in battle improve her accuracy and effectiveness in combat, providing a passive bonus to Agility. Grants no bonus if there are enemy heroes within 400 range.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/drow_ranger_marksmanship_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wfgqVIVWpr8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Drow Ranger is the epitome of archery prowess.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earth Spirit</Owner><Name>Boulder Smash</Name><Description>Earth Spirit smashes the target enemy or ally, sending them in the direction he is facing. If Earth Spirit targets an area, he will smash the nearest Stone Remnant in a 200 radius. The travelling unit or Remnant damages all enemy units it hits.  If an enemy is hit by a Stone Remnant, they are also stunned. Stone Remnants travel further than other units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earth_spirit_boulder_smash_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/18/14/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/EwR2Sxo5kKI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It is with the power of a mountain that Earth Spirit strikes his enemies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earth Spirit</Owner><Name>Rolling Boulder</Name><Description>Earth Spirit gathers himself into a boulder and, after a 0.6s delay, rolls toward the target location, damaging enemy units. He will stop if he collides with an enemy hero or is stunned. If he rolls over a Stone Remnant, he will travel further and faster, and enemies hit by the boulder will have their movement speed slowed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earth_spirit_rolling_boulder_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/12/8/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/YTpxu2tv0eo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Calling upon his connection to the land, the Earth Spirit draws loose stone to him, which forms a protective ball that he can use to roll short distances.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earth Spirit</Owner><Name>Geomagnetic Grip</Name><Description>Earth Spirit pulls the target Stone Remnant. Enemies struck by the gripped target will be silenced, and take damage if the gripped target is a Stone Remnant.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earth_spirit_geomagnetic_grip_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ad-ccVgez8I?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Like calls to like. Even the minerals found in the blood and bones of living beings are not immune to the call of the Earth Spirit.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earth Spirit</Owner><Name>Stone Remnant</Name><Description>Call a Stone Remnant to the target location.  Stones Remnants have no vision and are invulnerable, and can be used with Earth Spirit's abilities.  Calling a Stone Remnant consumes a charge, which recharge over time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earth_spirit_stone_caller_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/MAwGp4ooeDY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Earth Spirit calls forth a remnant of his stone army, long buried with him in the dark embrace of the Earth.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earth Spirit</Owner><Name>Enchant Remnant</Name><Description>Earth Spirit temporarily enchants a hero, granting them the properties of a Stone Remnant. After a short duration the remnant shatters, releasing the hero and damaging nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earth_spirit_petrify_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Kaolin uses the elemental power of the Earth to temporarily petrify living beings, so that they might be conscripted into his stone funerary army.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earth Spirit</Owner><Name>Magnetize</Name><Description>Magnetizes units in a small nearby area, causing them to take damage for a short duration. Magnetized heroes cause nearby Stone Remnants to explode, destroying the remnant and refreshing Magnetize's duration on all nearby enemies. This process can repeat multiple times. If an enemy hero is affected by silence or slows as a result of Geomagnetic Grip or Rolling Boulder, all magnetized heroes share the effects.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earth_spirit_magnetize_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100.000000</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100/90/80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vRo5fyoojWI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>At the Earth Spirit's call, the minerals in the blood and bones of his enemies rebel against the bodies they find themselves in.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earthshaker</Owner><Name>Fissure</Name><Description>Slams the ground with a mighty totem, creating an impassable ridge of stone while stunning and damaging enemy units along its line.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earthshaker_fissure_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/140/155/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vTbNwc5Tqwc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Nishian totem splits the world to its core with tectonic force.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earthshaker</Owner><Name>Enchant Totem</Name><Description>Empowers Earthshaker's totem, causing it to deal extra damage on the next attack.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earthshaker_enchant_totem_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 20/30/40/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OkSsLAN7mbk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Raigor's gorilla strength can destroy mountains.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earthshaker</Owner><Name>Aftershock</Name><Description>Causes the earth to shake underfoot, adding additional damage and stuns to nearby enemy units when Earthshaker casts his abilities.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earthshaker_aftershock_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2xcM8xccDIs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The earth trembles beneath the mighty footsteps of Raigor.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Earthshaker</Owner><Name>Echo Slam</Name><Description>Shockwaves travel through the ground, damaging enemy units.  Each enemy hit causes an echo to damage nearby units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/earthshaker_echo_slam_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 145/205/265</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 150/130/110</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1_C9UkV-27s?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Tectonic plates crack, mountains fold, and foes are crushed by the Echo Slam.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Elder Titan</Owner><Name>Echo Stomp</Name><Description>Elder Titan and his Astral Spirit both stomp the ground, damaging and knocking nearby enemy units unconscious around their locations.  The Elder Titan stomp deals physical damage, while the Spirit stomp deals magical damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/elder_titan_echo_stomp_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/13/12/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/yBDyBbeVK0k?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The force of creation still echoes in the stomp of the Titan.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Elder Titan</Owner><Name>Astral Spirit</Name><Description>Elder Titan sends forth his Astral Spirit, damaging any units it passes through.  When the spirit rejoins the Titan, it grants bonus damage and movement speed for each unit it damaged.

The Astral Spirit possesses the Echo Stomp, Return Spirit, and Natural Order abilities.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/elder_titan_ancestral_spirit_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OUUqiie5-Z8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Like the four fundamentals, Elder Titan exists across all planes at once and can draw other aspects of himself to assist in times of need.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Elder Titan</Owner><Name>Natural Order</Name><Description>Reduces all elements to their basic levels, removing base armor and magic damage resistance from nearby enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/elder_titan_natural_order_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>As it was at the beginning, Elder Titan makes it so again.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Elder Titan</Owner><Name>Return Astral Spirit</Name><Description>Returns the Astral Spirit to Elder Titan.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/elder_titan_return_spirit_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ql8H5QjhygM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Elder Titan</Owner><Name>Earth Splitter</Name><Description>Sends forth a jagged crack in front of Elder Titan. After 3 seconds, the crack implodes, slowing movement while dealing damage to each enemy based on their maximum life. Half of the damage dealt is Magical damage, while the other half is Physical damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/elder_titan_earth_splitter_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/175/225</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OWI9tNGa6dQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>That which he created, the titan tears asunder.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ember Spirit</Owner><Name>Searing Chains</Name><Description>Ember Spirit unleashes fiery bolas that wrap around nearby enemies, anchoring them in place and dealing damage each second.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ember_spirit_searing_chains_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/12/10/8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ca7UulcBAjs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Xin's harshest lessons often employed the use of red-hot chains.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ember Spirit</Owner><Name>Sleight of Fist</Name><Description>Ember Spirit dashes around with blazing speed, attacking all enemies in the targeted area of effect, then returning to his start location.  Deals bonus damage to heroes, and less damage to creeps.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ember_spirit_sleight_of_fist_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/22/14/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IwgpZwTKjco?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The studied warrior must whip and weave through its enemies, burning each without pause.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ember Spirit</Owner><Name>Flame Guard</Name><Description>Ember Spirit surrounds himself with a ring of fire that consumes incoming magic damage, leaving him unharmed.  Flame Guard deals damage per second in an area around Ember Spirit while Flame Guard is active.  If the shield is broken, the damage is also lost.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ember_spirit_flame_guard_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/zw9G68rgHt0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An enemy should never be allowed to approach without difficulty.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ember Spirit</Owner><Name>Activate Fire Remnant</Name><Description>Select the Fire Remnant to arrive at.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ember_spirit_activate_fire_remnant_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BmnxTs3P5Tg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With blazing speed does a spirit fly!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ember Spirit</Owner><Name>Fire Remnant</Name><Description>Ember Spirit generates Fire Remnant charges every 35 seconds, with a max of 3 charges.  Releasing a charge sends a Fire Remnant that runs to the target location at 2.5x Ember Spirit's speed.  Using Activate Fire Remnant, Ember Spirit can dash out to his Remnants, exploding them for area of effect damage.  The targeted Remnant will be arrived at last.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ember_spirit_fire_remnant_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/PbXcv1MG-go?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>By the spirit's power are Xin's teachings spread anew.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enchantress</Owner><Name>Untouchable</Name><Description>Enchantress beguiles her enemies, slowing their attacks when she is attacked.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enchantress_untouchable_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Bg3FV8n5HjI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>After attacking Aiushtha, most opponents are overwhelmed with guilt having attacked such a natural beauty.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enchantress</Owner><Name>Enchant</Name><Description>Enchantress charms an enemy. If the enemy is a hero, they are slowed. If the enemy is a creep, she brings it under her control. If cast on a creep already under her control, she refreshes its enchant duration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enchantress_enchant_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 65/65/65/65</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/24/18/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FEb9-pLBPXY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A true steward of the forest, Aiushtha befriends all within it - from lowly trolls to powerful centaurs.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enchantress</Owner><Name>Nature's Attendants</Name><Description>A cloud of wisps heals Enchantress and any friendly units nearby.  Lasts 10 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enchantress_natures_attendants_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/140/155/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/VCRqaqKZ4OY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Whimsical spirits of the woods possess a healing power that is quite subtle, but gains strength in numbers.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enchantress</Owner><Name>Impetus</Name><Description>Places an enchantment on each attack while activated, causing it to deal additional damage based on how far away the target is.  The farther the target, the greater the damage dealt.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enchantress_impetus_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 55/60/65</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FUkzdGUG_L8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While Aiushtha favors peaceful means, she is capable of a magical onslaught from a distance, her spears gaining energy from the natural life around her.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enigma</Owner><Name>Malefice</Name><Description>Focuses Enigma's power on a target, causing it to take damage and become repeatedly stunned for multiple instances.  An instance strikes every 2 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enigma_malefice_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/130/150/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/y0u1c81JqM0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Strange gravities pull at the core of those who would oppose you, holding them in place.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enigma</Owner><Name>Demonic Conversion</Name><Description>Transforms a creep into three fragments of Enigma himself.  These eidolons are all under Enigma's control, and repeated successful attacks cause them to multiply.  When this happens, the eidolons have their health restored.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enigma_demonic_conversion_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 170/170/170/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/9gj20AVAwE4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Enigma is capable of drawing aspects of himself from other dimensions - the result is a trio of dark eidolons that hunt the corporeal plane.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enigma</Owner><Name>Midnight Pulse</Name><Description>Steeps an area in dark resonance, damaging enemy units based on their max HP.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enigma_midnight_pulse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95/110/125/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/qrhVMKaO0NA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A section of the world slowly descends into the void.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Enigma</Owner><Name>Black Hole</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Summons a vortex that sucks in nearby enemy units.  Enemies affected by Black Hole cannot move, attack, or cast spells.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/enigma_black_hole_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 275/325/375</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 200/180/160</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FOKIcPeAYPw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The ground trembles as Enigma channels his ultimate vortex of destruction, a singularity with the power to end worlds.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Faceless Void</Owner><Name>Time Walk</Name><Description>Rushes to a target location while backtracking any damage taken the last 2 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/faceless_void_time_walk_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24/18/12/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/oW2YcRO3Njc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Darkterror tears a hole in time, passing through Claszureme, and appearing back in an instant.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Faceless Void</Owner><Name>Time Dilation</Name><Description>Faceless Void traps all nearby enemies in a time dilation field for 6 seconds, freezing their cooldowns and slowing their movement and attack speed by 8% for each cooldown frozen.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/faceless_void_time_dilation_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40/34/28/22</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Faceless Void</Owner><Name>Time Lock</Name><Description>Adds the chance for an attack to lock an enemy unit in time, stunning it and dealing bonus damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/faceless_void_time_lock_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZGW8iNF3Xiw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The strike of the Faceless Void lands with dimension shifting force.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Faceless Void</Owner><Name>Chronosphere</Name><Description>Creates a blister in spacetime, trapping all units caught in its sphere of influence and causes you to move very quickly inside it.  Only Faceless Void and any units he controls are unaffected.  Invisible units in the sphere will be revealed.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/faceless_void_chronosphere_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/225/300</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140/125/110</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/PnQqKogpmeU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When a rift opens to Claszureme, all poor souls caught within will likely never return.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Gyrocopter</Owner><Name>Rocket Barrage</Name><Description>Launches a salvo of rockets at nearby enemy units in a radius around the Gyrocopter.  Lasts 3 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/gyrocopter_rocket_barrage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/90/90/90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 7/6.50/6/5.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/JvJK0Y94TTU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Aurel's new craft has an increased payload for rockets, enhancing their rapid-fire capabilities.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Gyrocopter</Owner><Name>Homing Missile</Name><Description>Fires a homing missile to seek the targeted enemy unit. The missile gains speed over time, dealing damage and stunning when it impacts the target.  Homing Missile deals greater damage the further it has traveled.  Enemy units can destroy the missile before it reaches its target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/gyrocopter_homing_missile_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/130/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/17/14/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/nS_Qw-l6_OM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The biggest missile Aurel could possibly attach to his craft, The Bomb&amp;trade; has carefully calculated aerodynamics and explosives for maximum impact.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Gyrocopter</Owner><Name>Flak Cannon</Name><Description>Gyrocopter's attacks hit all enemy units in an area around it for a limited number of attacks.  Only the main target of attacks will receive attack bonuses such as Critical Strike.  Lasts 15 seconds or until the attacks are used.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/gyrocopter_flak_cannon_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vuAGkLLSJRE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>This newly revamped Gyrocopter has attached enough armaments to assault in a 360 degree radius.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Gyrocopter</Owner><Name>Call Down</Name><Description>Call down an aerial missile strike on enemy units in a target area.  Two missiles arrive in succession, the first dealing major damage and minor slow for 2 seconds; the second dealing minor damage and major slow for 4 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/gyrocopter_call_down_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/125/125</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 55/50/45</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/3YjjKN0VajU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>'Bombs Away!'</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Huskar</Owner><Name>Inner Vitality</Name><Description>Unlocks the regenerative power of a friendly unit, with healing based upon its primary attribute. If the target is below 40%, it will heal faster.  Lasts 16 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/huskar_inner_vitality_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 170/170/170/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/18/14/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Euh9XipSClI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While Huskar has little use for magic, this minor enchantment was learned from the Dazzle and the Dezun priests, to be used in times of great injury.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Huskar</Owner><Name>Burning Spear</Name><Description>Huskar sets his spears aflame, dealing damage over time with his regular attack.  Multiple attacks will stack additional damage.  Each attack drains some of Huskar's health.  Lasts 8 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/huskar_burning_spear_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OqiIX9VUBgk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Sacred Warrior ignites his weaponry after marking it with his own blood - causing far greater pain than he himself feels.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Huskar</Owner><Name>Berserker's Blood</Name><Description>Huskar's injuries feed his power, giving increased attack speed and magic damage resistance based on missing health.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/huskar_berserkers_blood_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/6Dx9pD12lEI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>After losing his birthright, Huskar gained a lethality in physical combat that is only heightened as his own blood is spilled.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Huskar</Owner><Name>Life Break</Name><Description>Huskar draws upon his health to break an enemy's life, leaping at a target within attack range to shatter a percentage of that hero's current health, and slowing them.  While leaping, Huskar is Spell Immune.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/huskar_life_break_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uL4iSDlCveo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>No matter the danger, Huskar thrusts himself into melees that only he can survive.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Quas</Name><Description>Allows manipulation of ice elements and grants a permanent strength bonus. Each Quas instance provides increased health regeneration.
</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_quas_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Wex</Name><Description>Allows manipulation of storm elements and grants a permanent agility bonus. Each Wex instance provides increased attack speed and movement speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_wex_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Exort</Name><Description>Allows manipulation of fire elements and grants a permanent intelligence bonus. Each Exort instance provides increased attack damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_exort_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Invoke</Name><Description>Combines the properties of the elements currently being manipulated to create a new spell for Invoker to use.  Click the help button to see the list of possible spells.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_invoke_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 20/40/60/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/17/12/5</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>So begins a new age of knowledge.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Cold Snap</Name><Description>Invoker draws the heat from an enemy, chilling them to their very core for a duration based on the level of Quas. The enemy will take damage and be briefly frozen. Further damage taken in this state will freeze the enemy again, dealing bonus damage. The enemy can only be frozen so often, but the freeze cooldown decreases based on the level of Quas.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_cold_snap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZPita8hr8MQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Sadron's Protracted Frisson.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Ghost Walk</Name><Description>Invoker manipulates the ice and electrical energies around him, rendering his body invisible. The elemental imbalance created as a consequence slows nearby enemies based on the level of Quas, and slows Invoker as well based on the level of Wex.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_ghost_walk_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/sjNjczESHgg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Myrault's Hinder-Gast.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Tornado</Name><Description>Unleashes a fast moving tornado that picks up enemy units in its path, suspending them helplessly in the air shortly before allowing them to plummet to their doom. Travels further based on the level of Wex. Holds enemies in the air for a duration based on the level of Quas. Deals base damage plus added damage based on levels in Wex.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_tornado_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/U7B3JkLVS0I?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Claws of Tornarus.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>EMP</Name><Description>Invoker builds up a charge of electromagnetic energy at a targeted location which automatically detonates after %delay% seconds. The detonation covers an area, draining mana based on the level of Wex. Deals damage for each point of mana drained.  If EMP drains mana from an enemy hero, Invoker gains 50% of the mana drained.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_emp_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/VF-cgzkXIMQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Endoleon's Malevolent Perturbation.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Alacrity</Name><Description>Invoker infuses an ally with an immense surge of energy, increasing their attack speed based on the level of Wex and their damage based on the level of Exort.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_alacrity_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 45</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/0BNznRqdlyA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Gaster's Mandate of Impetuous Strife.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Chaos Meteor</Name><Description>Invoker pulls a flaming meteor from space onto the targeted location. Upon landing, the meteor rolls forward, constantly dealing damage based on the level of Exort, and rolling further based on the level of Wex. Units hit by the meteor will also be set on fire for a short time, receiving additional damage based on the level of Exort.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_chaos_meteor_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 55</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/812PnlPitkE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Tarak's Descent of Fire.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Sun Strike</Name><Description>Sends a catastrophic ray of fierce energy from the sun at any targeted location, incinerating all enemies standing beneath it once it reaches the earth. Deals damage based on the level of Exort, however this damage is spread evenly over all enemies hit.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_sun_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 175</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5LZz3ZCHRW8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Harlek's Incantation of Incineration.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Forge Spirit</Name><Description>Invoker forges a spirit embodying the strength of fire and fortitude of ice. Damage, mana, and armor are based on the level of Exort while attack range, health, and duration are based on the level of Quas. The elemental's scorching attack is capable of melting the armor of enemy heroes. If both Quas and Exort are level 4 or higher, Invoker will create two spirits instead of one.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_forge_spirit_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/xMBMz64Icf8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Culween's Most Cunning Fabrications.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Ice Wall</Name><Description>Generates a wall of solid ice directly in front of Invoker for a duration based on the level of Quas. The bitter cold emanating from it greatly slows nearby enemies based on the level of Quas and deals damage each second based on the level of Exort.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_ice_wall_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 175</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cGVwehng5Zk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Killing Wall of Koryx.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Invoker</Owner><Name>Deafening Blast</Name><Description>Invoker unleashes a mighty sonic wave in front of him, dealing damage to any enemy unit it collides with based on the level of Exort. The sheer impact from the blast is enough to knock those enemy units back for a duration based on the level of Quas, then disarm their attacks for a duration based on the level of Wex.

If Quas, Wex, and Exort are all at max level, Deafening Blast becomes a non-targetable circular wave released in every direction around Invoker.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/invoker_deafening_blast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 300</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2dpFo8vn20U?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Buluphont's Aureal Incapacitator.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Tether</Name><Description>Tethers Io to an allied unit, granting bonus movement speed to both. When Io restores health or mana, tethered units target gain 1.5x the amount. Any enemy unit that crosses the tether is slowed. The tether breaks when the allied unit moves too far away, or Io cancels the tether.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_tether_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40/40/40/40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/KKF3zUQzMmQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The benevolent touch of Io brings strength from between the planes.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Break Tether</Name><Description>Break the link to the tethered unit.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_tether_break_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Spirits</Name><Description>Summon five particle spirits that dance in a circle around Io. If a particle collides with an enemy hero, it explodes, damaging all enemy units in an area around it.  Creeps take minor damage from touching a particle spirit, but do not cause them to explode.  When its duration ends, any remaining Spirits explode.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_spirits_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/130/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/18/16/14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/J_TjVQ4Jd7E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Io twists the particles of the universe with its unimaginable capabilities.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Overcharge</Name><Description>Io gains bonus attack speed and damage reduction, at the cost of draining a percentage of its current health and mana per second.  If Io is Tethered to an ally, that unit also gains the bonuses.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_overcharge_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 2</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cfr7ED0JB2g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Drawing on the energy of matter from all worlds, Io begins the unravelling of time.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Relocate</Name><Description>Teleports Io and any tethered ally to any location. After the spell expires Io and any tethered ally will return to their original location. Double-click to teleport to your team's base fountain.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_relocate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90/75/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/8X9-I9oTW3k?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Io is the embodiment of the mystery of the universe.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Spirits In</Name><Description>Calls the spirits closer to you. Can be toggled on and off.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_spirits_in_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Io</Owner><Name>Spirits Out</Name><Description>Sends the spirits farther away from you. Can be toggled on and off.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/wisp_spirits_out_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Jakiro</Owner><Name>Dual Breath</Name><Description>An icy blast followed by a wave of fire launches out in a path in front of Jakiro. The ice slows enemies, while the fire delivers damage over time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/jakiro_dual_breath_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 135/140/155/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/TF0T7EZuxqU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Pyrexae dragons have tremendously dangerous breath for each branch of the species; combining them is unimaginable.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Jakiro</Owner><Name>Ice Path</Name><Description>Creates a path of ice that stuns and damages enemies that touch it.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/jakiro_ice_path_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/11/10/9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/opuYKyouxJk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Jakiro's cunning right head calls upon its frozen heritage, glazing the earth with blistering cold.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Jakiro</Owner><Name>Liquid Fire</Name><Description>Jakiro burns his enemies in an area of effect with fire added to his attack, while slowing their attacks.

Liquid Fire is a Unique Attack Modifier, and does not stack with other Unique Attack Modifiers.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/jakiro_liquid_fire_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/15/10/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cdBmGuFveks?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The left maw of Jakiro opens, laying waste to any in its path.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Jakiro</Owner><Name>Macropyre</Name><Description>Jakiro exhales a wide line of lasting flames, which deals damage per second to any enemy units caught in the fire.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/jakiro_macropyre_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 220/330/440</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RWGgjf-GEy4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ice and fire combine to rip the battlefield to shreds with extreme temperatures.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Juggernaut</Owner><Name>Blade Fury</Name><Description>Causes a bladestorm of destructive force around Juggernaut, rendering him immune to magic and dealing damage to nearby enemy units.  Lasts 5 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/juggernaut_blade_fury_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/110/100/90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 42/34/26/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/0XijKqh4EJI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Yurnero's renowned katana techniques are feared by warriors and sorcerors alike.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Juggernaut</Owner><Name>Healing Ward</Name><Description>Summons a Healing Ward which heals all nearby allied units, based on their max health.  The Healing Ward moves at 420 movement speed after being summoned.  Lasts 25 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/juggernaut_healing_ward_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/125/130/135</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Wvh64L7ndTs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Of the rituals learned at the Isle of Masks, tending wounds with a bit of voodoo magic has proven to be quite useful.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Juggernaut</Owner><Name>Blade Dance</Name><Description>Gives Juggernaut a chance to deal double damage on each attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/juggernaut_blade_dance_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/J0i1IyxpvB0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The last remnant of his heritage's commitment to bladework, Yurnero ensures that the style is remembered.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Juggernaut</Owner><Name>Omnislash</Name><Description>Juggernaut leaps towards the target enemy unit with a damaging attack, and then slashes other nearby enemy units, dealing between 200-225 damage per slash.  Juggernaut is invulnerable for the duration.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/juggernaut_omni_slash_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/275/350</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 130/120/110</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/T4HOd3lIgyQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>'The fruits of discipline; with practice comes strength.'</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Illuminate</Name><Description>Channels light energy, building power the longer it's channeled.  Once released, a wave is sent forth that deals damage and gives vision in its path.  The longer it is channeled, the more damage is dealt.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_illuminate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/160/170/180</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/NjozLByuQgU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ezalor's hidden light reveals itself in marvelous fashion.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Mana Leak</Name><Description>Weakens an enemy's magical essence, causing them to lose mana as they move.  If the enemy loses all of its mana, it will be stunned.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_mana_leak_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/14/12/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/MjZIqs9cQks?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ezalor disrupts Primordial harmony, draining magical energy from those with poor constitution.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Chakra Magic</Name><Description>Restores mana to the target unit, increases its mana capacity, and reduces the cooldown of the next spell they cast.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_chakra_magic_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/35/45/55</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 17/16/15/14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/dSrcNmI_zBM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the same vein, Ezalor bestows his harmony among others.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Recall</Name><Description>After a short delay, teleports the targeted friendly hero to your location.  If the targeted friendly hero takes player based damage during this time, the ability is interrupted.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_recall_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gF0ZfzJJKn0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Walk towards the light.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Blinding Light</Name><Description>A blinding light flashes over the targeted area, knocking back and blinding the units in the area, causing them to miss attacks.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_blinding_light_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/16/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fWCofI864ho?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Primordial light turns the tides of battle in favor of Ezalor and his allies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Spirit Form</Name><Description>Ezalor temporarily turns his body luminescent, gaining various abilities.  Illuminate is now channeled by a separate spirit, and gains the Blinding Light and Recall abilities.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_spirit_form_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80/70/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/g7HXFJSWG98?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In a flash of light, Ezalor reveals his true nature.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Release Illuminate</Name><Description>Release the channel early.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_illuminate_end_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Keeper of the Light</Owner><Name>Illuminate</Name><Description>Channels light energy, building power the longer it's channeled.  Once released, a wave is sent forth that deals damage and gives vision in its path.  The longer it is channeled, the more damage is dealt.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/keeper_of_the_light_spirit_form_illuminate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/160/170/180</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Ezalor's hidden light reveals itself in marvelous fashion.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Kunkka</Owner><Name>Torrent</Name><Description>Summons a rising torrent that, after a short delay, hurls enemy units into the sky, stunning, dealing damage and slowing movement speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/kunkka_torrent_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2NeN4ToMrfY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An ancestral rush of water explodes from the center of the world, called upon by the Admiral.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Kunkka</Owner><Name>Tidebringer</Name><Description>Kunkka's legendary sword grants increased damage and cleaves a large area of effect in front of him for a single strike.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/kunkka_tidebringer_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13/10/7/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/GrJOoGLZyWg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A lost Claddish soul inhabits Kunkka's trusty Tidebringer, empowering it to destroy demons of the Cataract.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Kunkka</Owner><Name>X Marks the Spot</Name><Description>Targets a friendly or enemy Hero, marks their position with an X, and returns them to it after several seconds.  Kunkka can trigger the return at any time during the duration. Lasts twice as long on allied heroes.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/kunkka_x_marks_the_spot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 26/20/14/8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uF1OsHjC-tY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Admiral's set of arcane abilities includes some that can be used for battle as well as entertainment.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Kunkka</Owner><Name>Ghostship</Name><Description>Summons a ghostly ship that sails through the battle before smashing apart, damaging and stunning all enemies caught near the wreckage. Allied heroes touched by the Ghostship are given a swig of The Admiral's Rum, receiving bonus movement speed and a delayed reaction to 50% of all incoming damage.

Upgradeable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/kunkka_ghostship_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/175/225</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/50/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/lfnAIKZ6suE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The final ship of the Claddish Navy is nothing but a phantom, but it is all too real to the enemies of the Admiral.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Kunkka</Owner><Name>Return</Name><Description>Returns the marked hero to the X.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/kunkka_return_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Legion Commander</Owner><Name>Overwhelming Odds</Name><Description>Turns the enemies' numbers against them, dealing damage and granting you bonus movement speed per unit or per hero.  Deals bonus damage to illusions and summoned units as a percent of their current health.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/legion_commander_overwhelming_odds_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Xs5UU9xUQz4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The archers of Stonehall are ready at Tresdin's command.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Legion Commander</Owner><Name>Press The Attack</Name><Description>Removes debuffs and disables from the target friendly unit, and grants bonus attack speed and health regen for a short time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/legion_commander_press_the_attack_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/15/14/13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1xEPC7Eowsg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The rallying horn of the Bronze Legion is able to inspire any heart.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Legion Commander</Owner><Name>Moment of Courage</Name><Description>When attacked, Legion Commander has a chance to immediately counterattack with bonus lifesteal.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/legion_commander_moment_of_courage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 2.30/1.80/1.30/0.80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/WoCIKENH9-c?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Tresdin knows that an enemy's most vulnerable moment often follows their fiercest stroke.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Legion Commander</Owner><Name>Duel</Name><Description>Legion Commander and the target enemy hero are forced to attack each other for a short duration.  Neither hero can use items or abilities.  If either hero dies during the duration, the hero winning the Duel gains permanent bonus damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/legion_commander_duel_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uK5sUO2zCTU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>To face a soldier of Stonehall in single combat is a challenge few can resist.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Leshrac</Owner><Name>Split Earth</Name><Description>Splits the earth under enemies. Deals damage and stuns for a short duration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/leshrac_split_earth_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/125/140/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/pLGhNjlPRc8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Twisting nature to his vile will, the shifting earth consumes those unlucky enough to cross Leshrac's path.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Leshrac</Owner><Name>Diabolic Edict</Name><Description>Saturates the area around Leshrac with magical explosions that deal physical damage to enemy units and structures.  The fewer units available to attack, the more damage those units will take.  Deals 40% more damage to towers.  Lasts 10 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/leshrac_diabolic_edict_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95/120/135/155</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bwzT7xBaEHE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Chronoptic energy bursts from one plane to the other, evaporating anything it touches.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Leshrac</Owner><Name>Lightning Storm</Name><Description>Summons a lightning storm that blasts the target enemy unit, then strikes any nearby enemy units. Struck enemies are slowed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/leshrac_lightning_storm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bssFXEeOe4I?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Tormented Soul's mastery of the elements is evident in the massive storms that strike down armies before him.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Leshrac</Owner><Name>Pulse Nova</Name><Description>Creates waves of damaging energy around Leshrac, one per second, to damage nearby enemy units.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/leshrac_pulse_nova_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/90/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1IHJO2Tyl_0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>If necessary, the Tormented Soul can manipulate space time itself, ravaging lesser beings.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lich</Owner><Name>Frost Blast</Name><Description>Blasts the target enemy unit with damaging frost, dealing area damage and slowing movement and attack rates for 4 seconds.  The primary target takes the most damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lich_frost_nova_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/150/170/190</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bMuBB9l24ks?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Frost-mage Ethreain has not forgotten even the simplest of ice manipulation.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lich</Owner><Name>Ice Armor</Name><Description>Creates a shield around the target friendly unit or building, which adds armor and slows attacking units. Lasts 40 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lich_frost_armor_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/hfdMe2zPVhs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Originally crafted during his ambush for self-defense, the Lich is capable of enchanting others with a formidable defense of frost magic.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lich</Owner><Name>Sacrifice</Name><Description>Sacrifices a friendly creep and converts its current hit points into mana for Lich.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lich_dark_ritual_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/50/40/30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/_2zg_QNo1HQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It was not unheard of Ethreain to make examples out of those who contested his rule during his human life.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lich</Owner><Name>Chain Frost</Name><Description>Releases an orb of frost that bounces between nearby enemy units up to 10 times, slowing and damaging each time it hits.  The first target is mini-stunned.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lich_chain_frost_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/325/500</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120/90/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/VcWyGy_f5WU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Almost universally considered the ultimate in frost magic, Ethreain's orb of frozen death strikes fear into those who dare stand against him.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Rage</Name><Description>Launch into a maddened rage, becoming Spell Immune, 100% resistant to magic damage, and gaining increased attack speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_rage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ATQPbLwsReY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The madness and brutality of N'aix makes him a vicious and unrelenting foe in combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Feast</Name><Description>Lifestealer's attacks damage enemies and heal himself for a percentage of his target's current health.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_feast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Yhvj6uaaOBU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>After escaping from his cell in Devarque, N'aix subsisted on flesh and bones of those unfortunate to cross his path.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Open Wounds</Name><Description>Lifestealer rends an enemy unit, slowing the victim's movement speed and allowing all allies to regain health for a percentage of the damage they deal to that unit. All damage dealt will steal life, including damage from spells. The victim recovers movement speed over the duration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_open_wounds_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/110/110/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24/20/16/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/K3lZJEc_w_E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Fresh wounds and the scent of blood often draw out the scavengers to finish the job.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Assimilate</Name><Description>Lifestealer swallows an allied hero, allowing them to hide within him. Any healing Lifestealer receives is shared with the hero within. When an assimilated hero leaves Lifestealer, they erupt outward, damaging nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_assimilate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2eBe514DMBE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>How can Lifestealer resist the chance to sample an ally?</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Eject</Name><Description>Ejects an Assimilated hero, damaging nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_assimilate_eject_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Infest</Name><Description>Lifestealer infests the body of a target unit, becoming undetectable inside. He can then explode from the host body, dealing damage to nearby enemies. If the infested unit is an enemy creep or a neutral creep, he can take control of the unit's ability to move and attack, and when consumed the creep will heal Lifestealer's health equal to the creep's current health.  Does not work on enemy heroes.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_infest_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100/75/50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uvztpCPmci0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With this infestation, N'aix consumes the life blood of the host, restoring him back to full unholy power.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Control</Name><Description>Lifestealer seizes control of the host body's nervous system, allowing him to issue movement and attack orders from within.  Controlled units share Lifestealer's movement speed.  Cannot be used on heroes.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_control_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/j4DvBgSHwLE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lifestealer</Owner><Name>Consume</Name><Description>Lifestealer eats the host body from the inside out, exploding from within.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/life_stealer_consume_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lina</Owner><Name>Dragon Slave</Name><Description>Lina channels the breath of a dragon, sending out a wave of fire that scorches every enemy in its path.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lina_dragon_slave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/115/130/145</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2BShtaRLhhQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the scorched barren of Misrule, Lina learned to manipulate the fiery breath of the Desert Wyrm as a form of entertainment.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lina</Owner><Name>Light Strike Array</Name><Description>Summons a column of flames that damages and stuns enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lina_light_strike_array_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/110/120/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RBxhLSGnDig?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lina's essence allows her to focus the sun's energies, causing air to combust at will.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lina</Owner><Name>Fiery Soul</Name><Description>Grants bonus attack and movement speed each time Lina casts a spell. Stacks with itself. Lasts 10 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lina_fiery_soul_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/6R6-qq2PkIo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Dancing flames embody Lina's playful nature, bringing out her true blazing self.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lina</Owner><Name>Laguna Blade</Name><Description>Fires off a bolt of lightning at a single enemy unit, dealing massive damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lina_laguna_blade_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 280/420/680</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70/60/50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HbhoCPFse_c?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The air around Lina becomes so intensely torrid that it scorches a foe that comes too close with white-hot lightning.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lion</Owner><Name>Earth Spike</Name><Description>Rock spikes burst from the earth along a straight path. Enemy units are hurled into the air, then are stunned and take damage when they fall.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lion_impale_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/120/140/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IS20TjZpD2M?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Demon Witch exercises his demonic covenant, opening a fissure from hell.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lion</Owner><Name>Hex</Name><Description>Transforms an enemy unit into a harmless beast, with all special abilities disabled.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lion_voodoo_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/150/175/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/24/18/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1H8xWP_19Lo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lion is compelled to share his transfiguration, twisting the essence of those who oppose him.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lion</Owner><Name>Mana Drain</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Absorbs the magical energies of a target enemy unit by taking mana from it every second.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lion_mana_drain_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 10/10/10/10</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/12/8/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jclbhiTM7aA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lesser magi are nothing more than a source of magical restoration for the Demon Witch.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lion</Owner><Name>Finger of Death</Name><Description>Rips at an enemy unit, trying to turn it inside-out. Deals massive damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lion_finger_of_death_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/420/650</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 160/100/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/PoS308yRk5c?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lion's disfigured hand is also the source of his greatest power, capable of flooding victims with malefic force.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lone Druid</Owner><Name>Summon Spirit Bear</Name><Description>Summons a powerful Spirit Bear companion that can equip items.  If the bear moves 1100 distance away from the Lone Druid, it cannot attack.  Lone Druid suffers 10% of his max health as backlash damage if the Spirit Bear dies.  As the bear increases in levels, it can learn the Return, Entangling Claws, and Demolish abilities.  Spirit Bear does not benefit from attributes.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lone_druid_spirit_bear_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/SUdhkg7nFiM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Sylla's lifelong companion is symbiotic with his spirit and heart, coming to aid him in any time of need.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lone Druid</Owner><Name>Rabid</Name><Description>Increases the attack and movement speed of Lone Druid and the Spirit Bear.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lone_druid_rabid_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/AfvAbhr-If0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Bears are not commonly seen as being agile creatures, but can actually move rather quickly, especially when enraged.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lone Druid</Owner><Name>Savage Roar</Name><Description>Lone Druid roars fiercely causing nearby enemies to flee towards their base in terror. Their movement speed is increased by 20%.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lone_druid_savage_roar_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 38/32/26/20</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Sylla studies and masters the arts of the lost Bear Clan, enhancing his attunement with the wild.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lone Druid</Owner><Name>Battle Cry</Name><Description>Adds attack damage and armor to the Lone Druid as well as any nearby units under his control.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lone_druid_true_form_battle_cry_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/oytCi0vjT3c?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When Sylla cries in the forest, the reverberations are felt for a great distance.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lone Druid</Owner><Name>True Form</Name><Description>Lone Druid learns to morph himself into a raging bear, losing his ranged advantage and some base movement speed, but gaining melee power as well as the Battle Cry ability.  He can morph freely between druid and bear form.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lone_druid_true_form_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Y6IO-zXdiMk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The mighty bear is the king of the forest, possessing the throne through raw power.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lone Druid</Owner><Name>Druid Form</Name><Description>Return to Druid form.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lone_druid_true_form_druid_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ccYNZC6IRzk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Luna</Owner><Name>Lucent Beam</Name><Description>Calls a beam of lunar energy down upon an enemy, damaging and briefly stunning them.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/luna_lucent_beam_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ALMg8aRf7Xs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Selemene smites those who encroach upon the Nightsilver Woods.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Luna</Owner><Name>Moon Glaive</Name><Description>Empowers Luna's glaive, causing her attacks to bounce between enemy units. Deals less damage with each bounce.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/luna_moon_glaive_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/7TCPl446TcI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Carefully sharpened, Luna's boomerang-like weapon cuts a wide swath through enemy numbers.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Luna</Owner><Name>Lunar Blessing</Name><Description>Increases the damage dealt by attacks from Luna and nearby allied heroes. Luna is also blessed with increased vision range at night.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/luna_lunar_blessing_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1tKapRx4crk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Goddess of the Moon smiles upon her kin.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Luna</Owner><Name>Eclipse</Name><Description>Showers random nearby enemies with strikes from Luna's current level of Lucent Beam. These beams do not stun their targets, and there is a maximum number of times that a single target can be struck. Also turns day into night for 10 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/luna_eclipse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/200/250</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/pQKRK9KN5-U?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In times of great need, Selemene herself descends into the world, blocking out the light and hope of the opposed.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lycan</Owner><Name>Summon Wolves</Name><Description>Summons two wolves to fight for Lycan.  Level 2-4 wolves have Cripple, level 3-4 wolves have permanent invisibility, and level 4 wolves have 15 HP regen.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lycan_summon_wolves_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 145</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jgij5OMHj0M?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The very enchantment that twisted his being also summons canine familiars.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lycan</Owner><Name>Howl</Name><Description>Grants bonus damage to Lycan, all allied heroes and all units under their control.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lycan_howl_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 15/20/25/30</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50/45/40/35</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5vyHuopd3zQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Blood-curdling wolf cries signal to opponents that Banehallow is among them.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lycan</Owner><Name>Feral Impulse</Name><Description>Increases the damage and attack speed of Lycan and all units under his control.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lycan_feral_impulse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bmNQfQmSPzc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>His animalistic symbiosis with canine kind gives Banehallow enhanced reflexes and hunting capabilities.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Lycan</Owner><Name>Shapeshift</Name><Description>Lycan assumes his lupine form, granting him and his units critical strikes and added vision at night. During Shapeshift, Lycan and all units under his control move at increased speed, cannot be slowed and have a 40% chance to deal a critical strike doing 140% damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/lycan_shapeshift_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120/90/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/b2Uh7so6wiE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Forever a slave to his lycanthropy, Banehallow has come to accept his curse, and embrace his own savagery.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Magnus</Owner><Name>Shockwave</Name><Description>Magnus sends out a wave of force, damaging enemy units in a line.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/magnataur_shockwave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/90/90/90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10/9/8/7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FP8R8T5_kbc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Mt. Joerlak was a somewhat unstable mass, and Magnus has learned to channel its reverberations.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Magnus</Owner><Name>Empower</Name><Description>Gives an allied unit bonus damage and cleave on attack.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/magnataur_empower_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 30/40/50/60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/xjkhguSB_xY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With a deep bellow, Magnus displays his true power.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Magnus</Owner><Name>Skewer</Name><Description>Magnus rushes forward, goring enemy units on his massive tusk.  Heroes hit on the way will be dragged to the destination, then damaged and slowed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/magnataur_skewer_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/80/80/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/8zXtB2Ip1w8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Magnoceros horns are valuable in direct proportion to their danger to prospective merchants.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Magnus</Owner><Name>Reverse Polarity</Name><Description>Magnus changes properties of matter, sucking all nearby enemies in front of him and stunning them with a powerful slam and dealing damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/magnataur_reverse_polarity_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/250/300</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120/110/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/PMBM_CbFlyM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Magnus fights with the fury of the erupting Mt. Joerlak.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Medusa</Owner><Name>Split Shot</Name><Description>Medusa magically splits her shot into several arrows. These arrows deal a lower percent of her normal damage.

The extra targets will not receive other attack effects (such as critical strike) and Unique Attack Modifiers.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/medusa_split_shot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RTArHnkz0UQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>All who encounter the cursed Gorgon will feel her rage.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Medusa</Owner><Name>Mystic Snake</Name><Description>A mystic snake made of energy jumps from target to target dealing damage and stealing mana. After it reaches its last target, it returns to Medusa to replenish her with mana. The snake deals more damage per jump and steals 11% of the targets' total mana. Deals Pure damage to units petrified by Stone Gaze.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/medusa_mystic_snake_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 140/150/160/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BQw3_zhLK9o?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Gorgon's curse is her greatest strength.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Medusa</Owner><Name>Mana Shield</Name><Description>Creates a shield that absorbs 60% of the incoming damage in exchange for Medusa's mana.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/medusa_mana_shield_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OPryhacnXBg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While Medusa was not gifted with eternal life upon birth, her curse bestowed her with impressive defensive powers.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Medusa</Owner><Name>Stone Gaze</Name><Description>Any enemy units looking at Medusa will have their movement and attack speed slowed.  If 2 seconds of total time is accumulated looking at Medusa while Stone Gaze is active, that unit will turn to stone.  Petrified units are stunned, have 100% magic damage resistance, and take bonus physical damage.  If the petrified unit is an illusion, it is immediately killed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/medusa_stone_gaze_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/200/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/q_X57PFtq4o?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The beauty of Medusa is legendary.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Meepo</Owner><Name>Earthbind</Name><Description>Tosses a net at the target point, pinning down all enemy units.  Earthbind prevents invisibility, blink, and interrupts channeling.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/meepo_earthbind_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/16/12/8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/i1tAJ-RJ27Q?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Catching dinner in the Riftshadow Ruins can be quite the task.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Meepo</Owner><Name>Poof</Name><Description>Drawing mystical energies from the earth, a Meepo can teleport to another Meepo or itself after channeling for 1.5 seconds, dealing damage in both the departure and arrival locations.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/meepo_poof_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/10/8/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-alsToHm2BM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Sometimes breaking one of the Riftshadow Crystals can be just the trick for getting yourself out of a bind.  Or your other self.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Meepo</Owner><Name>Geostrike</Name><Description>Meepo enchants his weapon to deal damage per second, as well as slow the movement speed of the attacked unit.  Geostrikes from multiple Meepos stack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/meepo_geostrike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FNzYi2ViXMQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Keeping your pack light and having few but versatile tools is the best bet for survival.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Meepo</Owner><Name>Divided We Stand</Name><Description>Meepo summons an imperfect, semi-autonomous duplicate of himself, which can gain gold and experience as he does and shares his experience and abilities. However, the clones cannot wield any items but the boots that Meepo himself wears.  If any of the clones die, they all die.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/meepo_divided_we_stand_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/aa1ksGfZ6fY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Do I know you?</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Mirana</Owner><Name>Starstorm</Name><Description>Calls down a wave of meteors to damage nearby enemy units. The closest enemy unit to Mirana in a 425 radius will be struck a second time for 75% of the damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/mirana_starfall_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/120/140/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/d1FZp9axctE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Goddess breaks the strata to empower her Princess in the time of need.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Mirana</Owner><Name>Sacred Arrow</Name><Description>Fires a long-range arrow with deadly precision, which stuns and damages the first enemy unit it strikes. The stun duration ranges from 0.01 to 5 seconds, with bonus damage up to 140 added, based on the distance the arrow travels to its target. Instantly kills the first non-ancient creep it hits.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/mirana_arrow_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 17</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BG-WZoCv3PA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lunar energies make the Princess of the Moon's arrows more deadly than most.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Mirana</Owner><Name>Leap</Name><Description>Mirana leaps forward into battle, empowering allied units with a ferocious roar that grants bonus attack and movement speed. Speed bonus lasts 10 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/mirana_leap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40/35/30/20</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/26/22/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gB6cL5h6DgI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Both friend and foe alike recognize Mirana's iconic white beast in the heat of battle.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Mirana</Owner><Name>Moonlight Shadow</Name><Description>Turns Mirana and all allied heroes invisible. If a hero is revealed, invisibility will restore after the fade delay as long as Moonlight Shadow's duration has not expired.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/mirana_invis_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140/120/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FjieOflgUg0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Her tenure with Selemene allows Mirana to eclipse the ground, wrapping her allies in a cloak of shadows.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Waveform</Name><Description>Morphling dissolves into liquid and surges forward, damaging enemy units in his path.  Morphling is invulnerable during Waveform.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_waveform_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 140/155/160/165</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/qLvbyl4-ffQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A torrential flood takes enemies by force.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Adaptive Strike</Name><Description>Launches a surge of water toward an enemy unit, stunning the target while dealing base damage plus additional damage based on Morphling's agility times a multiplier.  If Morphling's agility is 50% higher than strength, the maximum damage and the minimum stun is dealt. If his strength is 50% higher than his agility, the maximum stun and minimum damage are dealt.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_adaptive_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/90/80/70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/n0r5iigJ8bY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Morphling calls upon his elements to crush his opponents with waves.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Morph (Agility Gain)</Name><Description>Morphling shifts its form, pulling points from Strength and pouring them into Agility. The process is reversible.  Additional points in Morph increase the rate of stat change.  Passively grants bonus Agility.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_morph_agi_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/otjA8B6i6Ak?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Shifting water makes it difficult to discern the nature of Morphling.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Morph (Strength Gain)</Name><Description>Morphling shifts its form, pulling points from Agility and pouring them into Strength. The process is reversible.  Additional points in Morph increase the rate of stat change.  Passively grants bonus Strength.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_morph_str_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gLJQ21TtGII?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Shifting water makes it difficult to discern the nature of Morphling.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Hybrid</Name><Description>Morphling creates a hybrid replication of a target allied hero, which can cast all of that hero's current, non-ultimate abilities. Enemies are able to see which unit is a hybrid.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_hybrid_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/AF35Myvmoag?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Replicate</Name><Description>Morphling replicates any hero, friend or foe, dealing 80% of the original Hero's outgoing damage while taking 100% of any incoming damage.  At any time, Morphling can instantly take the position of the Replicate for 150 mana. If Morphling dies, the Replicate will expire.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_replicate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZZRC6hORDWc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Staring into Morphling produces a reflection that mimics the beholder.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Morphling</Owner><Name>Morph Replicate</Name><Description>Morphling switches into his replication, instantly taking its position.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/morphling_morph_replicate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/150/150</Mana><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2kQLOqN-wUM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Naga Siren</Owner><Name>Mirror Image</Name><Description>Creates three images of Naga Siren under her control.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/naga_siren_mirror_image_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/80/90/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/v70MJ69BXHc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Slithice, while being strong in her own right, is notoriously hard to track down.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Naga Siren</Owner><Name>Ensnare</Name><Description>Interrupts the target and traps them in place, preventing movement or blinking.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/naga_siren_ensnare_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/EmB60RoN_Do?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The only way to escape the onslaught of a Slithereen is to never oppose one in the first place.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Naga Siren</Owner><Name>Rip Tide</Name><Description>The Naga Siren and her images hit all nearby units with a damaging wave of water that lowers armor for 8 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/naga_siren_rip_tide_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/kOUYkdJzR0E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A torrent from the Deep Ones crushes the defenses of the Siren's enemies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Naga Siren</Owner><Name>Song of the Siren</Name><Description>All enemies in range of the Naga Siren are put into a magical stasis where they cannot act or be attacked. Using Song of the Siren again will end the duration early.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/naga_siren_song_of_the_siren_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 180/120/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/P5Lmhv9mBR4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Slithice's powerful voice enchants leagues of opponents, while calling her Slithereen kin in a time of need.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Naga Siren</Owner><Name>Song of the Siren End</Name><Description>Release enemy units from your song so they can be targeted again.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/naga_siren_song_of_the_siren_cancel_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nature's Prophet</Owner><Name>Sprout</Name><Description>Sprouts a ring of trees around a unit, trapping it in place.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/furion_sprout_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/90/110/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 11/10/9/8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IKC9k4noGgI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Verdant overgrowth is a common ailment reported by Nature's Prophet's attackers.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nature's Prophet</Owner><Name>Teleportation</Name><Description>Teleports to any point on the map.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/furion_teleportation_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50/40/30/20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/4Z6E1mANiYY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Prophet keeps his sentinel over the forest, protecting it when in need.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nature's Prophet</Owner><Name>Nature's Call</Name><Description>Converts an area of trees into Treants. Treants have 550 health and deal 30-34 damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/furion_force_of_nature_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 160/160/160/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 37</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/h-4uJF0-P6w?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Verodicia bestowed the Prophet with the ability to summon the Treant Guard, a mythical sentient army of the wild.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nature's Prophet</Owner><Name>Wrath of Nature</Name><Description>Damaging energy bounces around the map, striking enemies close to the cast point that are in vision. Each enemy hit beyond the first adds damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/furion_wrath_of_nature_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 175/225/275</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90/75/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gqPn_GVmLDY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Nature's Prophet calls Verodicia's fury to strike down those who might ravage the wilderness.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Necrophos</Owner><Name>Death Pulse</Name><Description>Necrophos releases a wave of death around him, dealing damage to enemy units and healing allied units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/necrolyte_death_pulse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/145/165/185</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8/7/6/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/T0DSPAolJJI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Combining his monk heritage with his newfound affinity for plague has a menacing result.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Necrophos</Owner><Name>Heartstopper Aura</Name><Description>Necrophos stills the hearts of his opponents, causing nearby enemy units to lose a percentage of their max health over time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/necrolyte_heartstopper_aura_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/CBznxq8uUJM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Those who come within a short distance of Necrophos can feel pestilence and plague in the air.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Necrophos</Owner><Name>Sadist</Name><Description>Necrophos gains health and mana regeneration for every unit he kills. Hero kills grant 10 times the regen bonus.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/necrolyte_sadist_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/SMMewm8ck-w?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Poor souls who succumb to Rotund'jere's plagues are recycled for future use.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Necrophos</Owner><Name>Reaper's Scythe</Name><Description>Stuns the target enemy hero, then deals damage based on how much life it is missing. Heroes killed by Reaper's Scythe will have 10 seconds added to their respawn timer. Any kill under this effect is credited to Necrophos.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/necrolyte_reapers_scythe_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 175/340/500</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100/85/70</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/q-yTpAiBoFM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The amount of death and suffering in the air increases the power of Necrophos's plague magic.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Night Stalker</Owner><Name>Void</Name><Description>Creates a damaging void that slows an enemy unit and deals damage.  Void also mini-stuns, interrupting channeling abilities. The slowing effect lasts longer at night.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/night_stalker_void_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HPu40Ahpefw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Balanar creates a vortex of infinite night, tearing opponents violently into the eternal darkness that once was.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Night Stalker</Owner><Name>Crippling Fear</Name><Description>Night Stalker horrifies the target enemy Hero, causing it to miss attacks and become silenced.  The effect lasts longer at night.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/night_stalker_crippling_fear_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1i9z1rYqmZg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A vision of the twisted maw of Balanar etches itself into the minds of the poor souls unlucky enough to cross his path.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Night Stalker</Owner><Name>Hunter in the Night</Name><Description>Night Stalker is in his element at night, attacking and moving with great swiftness.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/night_stalker_hunter_in_the_night_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/S2Br_dswVZY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The hunting prowess of Balanar improves as the night beckons.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Night Stalker</Owner><Name>Darkness</Name><Description>Night Stalker smothers the sun and summons instant darkness, so that he might use his powers at their fullest. While Darkness is in effect, enemy heroes, units, wards and buildings have their vision range reduced to 675. 

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/night_stalker_darkness_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 160/120/80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/xuCoHHo_pJw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It is a humbling sight to see when the mightiest of warriors become afraid of the dark.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nyx Assassin</Owner><Name>Impale</Name><Description>Rock spikes burst from the earth along a straight path. Enemy units are hurled into the air, then are stunned and take damage when they fall.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nyx_assassin_impale_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95/115/135/155</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bi-zUW9TbxU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>All zealot scarabs possess intimate knowledge of underground pathways, using them to their advantage.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nyx Assassin</Owner><Name>Mana Burn</Name><Description>Destroys the target hero's mana equal to a multiplier of its Intelligence, and deals damage equal to the mana burned.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nyx_assassin_mana_burn_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 28/20/12/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Vdnc20VlniA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The tome in Ultimyr describes one scarab with the ability eat away at the mind of lesser beings.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nyx Assassin</Owner><Name>Spiked Carapace</Name><Description>When activated while above ground, Spiked Carapace reflects and negates damage dealt to Nyx Assassin (max once from each source), as well as stunning the source of the damage. Activating Spiked Carapace will not break Vendetta invisibility.

While Burrowed, Spiked Carapace instantly stuns nearby enemies when cast.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nyx_assassin_spiked_carapace_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40/40/40/40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/18/14/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ItgZ-Dd1Lj0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While their carapace is relatively thin, it's guarded by a retractable field of razor-sharp spikes.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nyx Assassin</Owner><Name>Burrow</Name><Description>Nyx Assassin buries himself beneath the battlefield over a short duration. Once burrowed, Spiked Carapace instantly stuns nearby enemies when cast, the range of Mana Burn and Impale is increased, and Impale's cooldown is decreased. While burrowed, Nyx Assassin is stationary, unable to attack, and invisible. His health and mana regeneration are also increased, and he gains damage reduction from all damage sources.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nyx_assassin_burrow_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>Some castes of zealot scarab are known to create small burrows to lie in wait, ready to ambush their prey.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nyx Assassin</Owner><Name>Unburrow</Name><Description>Emerge from the burrow.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nyx_assassin_unburrow_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Some castes of zealot scarab are known to create small burrows to lie in wait, ready to ambush their prey.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Nyx Assassin</Owner><Name>Vendetta</Name><Description>Allows Nyx Assassin to become invisible and gain a speed bonus.  If Nyx Assassin attacks to break the invisibility, massive bonus damage is dealt with the attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nyx_assassin_vendetta_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 160/210/260</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70/60/50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/XLNvigI8GT0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The scarab kills for the glory of his queen.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ogre Magi</Owner><Name>Fireblast</Name><Description>Blasts an enemy unit with a wave of fire, dealing damage and stunning the target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ogre_magi_fireblast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/85/95/105</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/sEWGzFIZQtU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Ogre Magi is easily amused, entertained for hours by playing with fire.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ogre Magi</Owner><Name>Ignite</Name><Description>Drenches a target in volatile chemicals, causing it to burst into flames. The target is in immense pain, taking damage and moving more slowly.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ogre_magi_ignite_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Nj6AXWAl2s0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Batter up!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ogre Magi</Owner><Name>Bloodlust</Name><Description>Incites a frenzy in a friendly unit, increasing its movement speed and attack speed. Can be cast on towers.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ogre_magi_bloodlust_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/J3py9ylBrjQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>'Running's not as fun as hitting... Not one bit fun.'</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ogre Magi</Owner><Name>Unrefined Fireblast</Name><Description>Blasts an enemy unit with a wave of fire, dealing damage and stunning the target. Its mana cost is 60% of Ogre Magi's current mana.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ogre_magi_unrefined_fireblast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 400</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/tJgO6bPCNBk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The 'who-casts-spell-first' argument between himself is solved simply by both casting at once.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ogre Magi</Owner><Name>Multicast</Name><Description>Enables Ogre Magi to cast his spells multiple times with each use, while also granting his spells greater potency:
Fireblast has its cooldown decreased, its range increased, and its mana cost increased.
Ignite hits enemies in an area, its range is increased, and it may be cast onto random nearby enemies when used.
Bloodlust has its cooldown reduced, and may be cast on random nearby allies when used.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ogre_magi_multicast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>Despite being largely incapacitated by his IQ, the Ogre Magi's success in battle is attributed to pure skill.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Omniknight</Owner><Name>Purification</Name><Description>Instantly heals a friendly unit and damages all nearby enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/omniknight_purification_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/120/140/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ohj0Wq-YJAQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Priests of the Omniscience are adept at removing impurities from fellow warriors.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Omniknight</Owner><Name>Repel</Name><Description>Creates a divine barrier around a target unit which grants them Spell Immunity and 100% resistance to Magic Damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/omniknight_repel_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/rlLqiwxB4ko?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When faced with the pit of sacrifice, Purist's resilience to magic was tested and affirmed.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Omniknight</Owner><Name>Degen Aura</Name><Description>Greatly degenerates the movement and attack capabilities of enemy units that stray too near.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/omniknight_degen_aura_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/P3yU81TYOYU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The holy embodiment of Purist Thunderwrath is enough to weaken those of lesser faith.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Omniknight</Owner><Name>Guardian Angel</Name><Description>Omniknight summons a Guardian Angel that grants immunity from physical damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/omniknight_guardian_angel_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/175/250</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 150</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/SIBSA30sMz4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The All Seeing One casts down his protection over those that Purist calls friend.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Oracle</Owner><Name>Fortune's End</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Gathers Oracle's power into a bolt of scouring energy that, when released, damages, stops movement, and purges enemies of buffs in an area around the target. If target is an ally it will only purge. Can be channeled for up to 2.5 seconds. The stop duration is equal to the time spent channeling.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/oracle_fortunes_end_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15/12/9/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uoC4rmz5pL4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The astral orb crackles with power while raw energy lances out, temporarily disrupting an enemy's connection to their own body.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Oracle</Owner><Name>Fate's Edict</Name><Description>Oracle enraptures a target, disarming them and granting them 100% magic damage resistance. Can be cast on allies and enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/oracle_fates_edict_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/13/10/7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-5MLuLQ92_w?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An unbreakable prophecy resounds: a chosen ally shall briefly suffer no magics.  Other kinds of suffering however...</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Oracle</Owner><Name>Purifying Flames</Name><Description>Burns away impurities, dealing heavy magic damage to the target before causing them to regenerate health over time. The amount of health regenerated over its duration exceeds the amount of initial damage. Can be cast on enemies and allies.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/oracle_purifying_flames_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/60/70/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 2.25</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/YP2ZXzx6kX4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Like a hall of mirrors might amplify the light of a single candle, the shattered walls of the universe can transform the light of prophecy into a burning torch.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Oracle</Owner><Name>False Promise</Name><Description>Temporarily alters an ally's destiny, delaying any healing or damage taken until False Promise ends. Any healing that is delayed by False Promise is doubled. Removes most negative status effects and disables on initial cast.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/oracle_false_promise_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 100/65/30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/q_OHyoGf9Ns?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Foes and false prophets oft make lies of men's fates.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Outworld Devourer</Owner><Name>Arcane Orb</Name><Description>Adds extra pure damage to Outworld Devourer's attacks, based on his remaining mana pool. Steals 1 intelligence for 80 seconds per hit when attacking an enemy hero. Arcane Orb also does bonus damage to summoned units and illusions.

Arcane Orb is a Unique Attack Modifier, and does not stack with other Unique Attack Modifiers.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/obsidian_destroyer_arcane_orb_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/120/140/160</Mana><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/zhA1HK7cy5g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Harbinger's outworldly knowledge allows it to tap into the ebb and flow of all spiritual energy, infusing it into his being.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Outworld Devourer</Owner><Name>Astral Imprisonment</Name><Description>Places a target unit into an astral prison. The hidden unit is invulnerable and disabled. When the astral prison implodes, it deals 100 damage to enemies in a 400 radius around the target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/obsidian_destroyer_astral_imprisonment_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/140/160/180</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/18/14/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fJhBCZ6TrP0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Locked away in the pocket between this world and the Outworld, victims realize their infantile knowledge and mortality.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Outworld Devourer</Owner><Name>Essence Aura</Name><Description>Whenever nearby allied Heroes or Outworld Devourer itself casts a spell, it gains a chance to restore a percentage of its mana pool.  Outworld Devourer also passively gains a bonus to its base mana pool.  Several skills with no cooldown and toggled spells cannot trigger Essence Aura.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/obsidian_destroyer_essence_aura_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jXW4mXUgZTw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The crystals of the Outworld produce arcane power, and the Harbinger channels it into the world of mortals.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Outworld Devourer</Owner><Name>Sanity's Eclipse</Name><Description>Unleashes a psychic blast that removes 40% of the mana from affected heroes, while also damaging them based on the difference between the affected hero's Intelligence and Outworld Devourer's. If an enemy hero has the same or higher Intelligence than Outworld Devourer, Sanity's Eclipse will not cause damage. Sanity's Eclipse can hit units trapped by Astral Imprisonment.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/obsidian_destroyer_sanity_eclipse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 175/250/325</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 160</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Z4dnT-tAOac?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>When an Outworld crystal ruptures, cataclysmic energies are released, and the reverberations of this power are felt interdimensionally.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Assassin</Owner><Name>Stifling Dagger</Name><Description>Throws a dagger slowing the enemy unit's movement speed, dealing 75+25% of Phantom Assassin's attack damage as physical damage and applying attack effects from items and abilities.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_assassin_stifling_dagger_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 30/25/20/15</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/i5m8Cb2yyUE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The first skill learned by the Sisters of the Veil often signals an incoming hit.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Assassin</Owner><Name>Phantom Strike</Name><Description>Teleports to a unit, friendly or enemy, and grants bonus attack speed while attacking if it's an enemy unit.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_assassin_phantom_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/11/8/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vzvGCgwQoOA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Mortred's silken veil is the last thing her unfortunate target sees.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Assassin</Owner><Name>Blur</Name><Description>Phantom Assassin focuses inward, increasing her ability to evade enemy attacks, and allowing her to blur her body to disappear from the enemy team's minimap when far from enemy heroes.

Stacks diminishingly with other sources of Evasion.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_assassin_blur_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/EDaQVTmxsNM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Meditation allows a Veiled Sister to carefully anticipate her opponents in combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Assassin</Owner><Name>Coup de Grace</Name><Description>Phantom Assassin refines her combat abilities, gaining a chance of delivering a devastating critical strike to enemy units. Stifling Dagger shares the same critical strike chance.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_assassin_coup_de_grace_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/A0dUz8U6nDM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A divine strike, Mortred honors her opponent by choosing them for death.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Lancer</Owner><Name>Spirit Lance</Name><Description>Sends a magical spirit lance to a target enemy unit that damages and slows, while summoning an illusory phantom to attack the unit.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_lancer_spirit_lance_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/130/135/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/kAQg8iTEvWA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Azwraith's proficiency at spearing his family's meal of fish is proving quite useful in the battlefield.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Lancer</Owner><Name>Doppelganger</Name><Description>Phantom Lancer briefly vanishes from the battlefield. After 1 second, Phantom Lancer and any of his nearby illusions reappear at a random position within the targeted location, along with two additional doppelgangers. The two added doppelgangers have different properties: one takes normal damage and deals none, while the other takes 600% damage and deals 20% damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_lancer_doppelwalk_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25/20/15/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/_HLFI68EP-Y?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Dread Magus Vorn's death imbued the Phantom Lancer with the ability to bend and fracture all spectrums of light.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Lancer</Owner><Name>Phantom Rush</Name><Description>When targetting an enemy for an attack, Phantom Lancer quickly charges into range. Phantom Lancer's illusions also have this ability.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_lancer_phantom_edge_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/12/8/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/_bfdarOBBU8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Azwraith knows that on the field of battle, speed can mean everything.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phantom Lancer</Owner><Name>Juxtapose</Name><Description>Phantom Lancer has a chance to fracture his presence, creating an illusion of himself. Illusions also have a chance to fracture further. Illusions created from Phantom Lancer last for 8 seconds, while illusions created from other illusions last 4 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phantom_lancer_juxtapose_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/rti6D9kGcKY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Each of Azwraith's lance attacks feels like two from a normal warrior; or three; or four...</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Icarus Dive</Name><Description>Phoenix dives forward in an arc with a fixed distance in the targeted direction, dealing damage over time and slowing the movement speed of any units it comes into contact with, and then orbiting back to its original position. If Phoenix casts Supernova, the dive ends.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_icarus_dive_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 36</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/PUkHORxk8J4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Though no stranger to travelling the cosmic void, soaring within an atmosphere offers unique pleasures.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Fire Spirits</Name><Description>Summons 4 fire spirits that circle around Phoenix. Each spirit can be launched independently at a targeted area of effect. Affected enemy units take damage over time and have their attack speed greatly reduced.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_fire_spirits_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45/40/35/30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/r1MosnS5858?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The ever-collapsing core of Phoenix often emits short-lived bursts of conscious light.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Sun Ray</Name><Description>Phoenix expels a beam of light at the cost of its own health. The beam damages enemies and heals allies for a base amount plus a percentage of their health. The percentage increases as the beam continues to fire.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_sun_ray_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 26</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HZAiHWRNCjw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The vent through which such stellar energy flows is mere atoms wide.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Supernova</Name><Description>The Phoenix willingly ends its current life for the chance to be reborn. Transforms into a burning sun that scorches enemies in a huge area. The sun can be destroyed by attacks from enemy Heroes. After 6 seconds the sun explodes, stunning all nearby enemies while restoring Phoenix to full health and mana with refreshed abilities.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_supernova_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/200/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 110</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/DkFkvLCYeCY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The solar crucible of a Supernova may be fatal, yet from its flames arise new beacons to wander infinity.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Launch Fire Spirit</Name><Description>Each fire spirit can be launched independently at a targeted area of effect. Affected enemy units take damage over time and have their attack speed greatly reduced. Reveals the area it strikes for 1 second.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_launch_fire_spirit_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>PKAWW! BOOM</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Stop Icarus Dive</Name><Description>Immediately cancels the dive.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_icarus_dive_stop_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>SCREE!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Stop Sun Ray</Name><Description>Immediately stops the Sun Ray.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_sun_ray_stop_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>CHIRP!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Phoenix</Owner><Name>Toggle Movement</Name><Description>Toggles slow forward movement during Sun Ray firing.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/phoenix_sun_ray_toggle_move_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>SQAWRK!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Puck</Owner><Name>Illusory Orb</Name><Description>Puck launches a magic orb that floats in a straight path, damaging enemy units along the way. At any point, Puck may teleport to the orb's location using Ethereal Jaunt.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/puck_illusory_orb_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/100/120/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/13/12/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/St6DymTgpjc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The playful Faerie Dragon delights in confusing others, vanishing and reappearing where unexpected.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Puck</Owner><Name>Waning Rift</Name><Description>Puck releases a burst of faerie dust that deals damage and silences enemy units nearby.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/puck_waning_rift_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/110/120/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/15/14/13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/kM91nc9KFzg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With a mischievous grin, Puck spreads its enchanted powder which disrupts magical flow.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Puck</Owner><Name>Phase Shift</Name><Description>Puck briefly shifts into another dimension where it is immune from harm.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/puck_phase_shift_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fQM9lmdO3a4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With a quip and flash, Puck returns to the alien dimension from whence it came.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Puck</Owner><Name>Ethereal Jaunt</Name><Description>Teleports Puck to a flying Illusory Orb.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/puck_ethereal_jaunt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/lh-wFZu85N0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Puck</Owner><Name>Dream Coil</Name><Description>Creates a coil of volatile magic that latches onto enemy Heroes, stunning them for 0.5 seconds and damaging them.  If the enemy hero stretches the coil by moving too far away, it snaps, stunning and dealing additional damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/puck_dream_coil_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/150/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 75</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/DyAcAYncwXE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Faerie Dragon sows confusion by forcing its enemies to vividly dream about their own mortality.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pudge</Owner><Name>Meat Hook</Name><Description>Launches a bloody hook toward a unit or location. The hook will snag the first unit it encounters, dragging the unit back to Pudge and dealing damage if it is an enemy.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pudge_meat_hook_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14/13/12/11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5Y_PSSK5bDc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Butcher's hook is a symbolic nightmare, its curved blade a frightening reminder of his slaughterous intent.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pudge</Owner><Name>Rot</Name><Description>A toxic cloud that deals intense damage and slows movement--harming not only enemy units but Pudge himself.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pudge_rot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bzyCOE9V3tI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A foul odor precedes a toxic, choking gas, emanating from the Butcher's putrid, ever-swelling mass.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pudge</Owner><Name>Flesh Heap</Name><Description>Gives Pudge resistance to magic damage, as well as bonus strength that increases each time Pudge kills an enemy Hero or it dies in his vicinity.  Flesh Heap is retroactive, meaning it can gain charges before it is skilled, which then become active.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pudge_flesh_heap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>The Butcher gives new meaning to the words 'meat shield.'</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pudge</Owner><Name>Dismember</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Pudge chows down on an enemy unit, disabling it and dealing damage over time. Pudge gets healed for the same amount he damages. Lasts 3 seconds on Heroes, 6 seconds on creeps.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pudge_dismember_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/130/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/25/20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/e46jjuekNeU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>'When I'm through with these vermin, they'll be fit for a pie!'</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pugna</Owner><Name>Nether Blast</Name><Description>An exploding pulse deals damage to enemies and structures in the area.  Deals half damage to structures.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pugna_nether_blast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 85/105/125/145</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/S-CNAxuxwbU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Arts of Oblivion include a deafening blast of emerald flames from the Nether Reaches.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pugna</Owner><Name>Decrepify</Name><Description>A powerful banishing spell that slows a unit and renders it unable to attack or be attacked. Afflicted units take extra magic damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pugna_decrepify_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15/12/9/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vslnhbjQiXw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A now-mastered relic from his childhood, Pugna delights in banishing others into the Nether Realm, whether for good, evil, or simple enjoyment.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pugna</Owner><Name>Nether Ward</Name><Description>Pugna places a Nether Ward at the target location. The ward reduces the mana regeneration of nearby enemy heroes, and will fire at any enemy hero who casts a spell. Nether Ward deals damage equal to the damage multiplier times the mana spent by the enemy hero.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pugna_nether_ward_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/80/80/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1GLjEtZRA7M?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>While at the lamasery for the Arts of Oblivion, Pugna learned to dominate his classmates with a simple ward charged with Nether magic.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Pugna</Owner><Name>Life Drain</Name><Description>CHANNELED - When cast on an enemy, Pugna drains health from the target enemy unit to heal himself. If Pugna has full HP, and the enemy target is a Hero, Life Drain will restore mana instead.

When cast on an ally, Pugna will drain his own health into his ally.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/pugna_life_drain_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/175/225</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/G9pGWvXj0aE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Pugna has truly become more powerful than even the grandmaster of Oblivion.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Queen of Pain</Owner><Name>Shadow Strike</Name><Description>Hurls a poisoned dagger which deals large initial damage, and then deals damage over time. The poisoned unit has its movement speed slowed for 15 seconds.  An instance of damage is dealt every 3 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/queenofpain_shadow_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/12/8/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Qnv17DFLvbc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Akasha's envenomed dagger allows her to delight in the drawn out suffering of her victims.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Queen of Pain</Owner><Name>Blink</Name><Description>Short distance teleportation that allows Queen of Pain to move in and out of combat.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/queenofpain_blink_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/60/60/60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 15/12/9/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZaFlZ5YZhbw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Secret Queen lives up to her title, making her pain impossible to escape.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Queen of Pain</Owner><Name>Scream Of Pain</Name><Description>The Queen of Pain lets loose a piercing scream around her, damaging nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/queenofpain_scream_of_pain_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Jb_qB9V9jpE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The sultry voice of Akasha beckons her opponents while stealing their souls.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Queen of Pain</Owner><Name>Sonic Wave</Name><Description>Creates a gigantic wave of sound in front of Queen of Pain, dealing heavy damage to all enemy units in its wake.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/queenofpain_sonic_wave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 250/360/500</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 135</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/nfaHlauWaog?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Her most exquisite of all of torments, Akasha's Sonic Wave puts her poor foes out of their misery.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Razor</Owner><Name>Plasma Field</Name><Description>Releases a wave of energetic plasma that grows in power as it expands, but also zaps on contraction, dealing damage to enemy units caught in its path. Damage increases with distance from Razor.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/razor_plasma_field_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/125/125/125</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/3wvYOe_TxFY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Lightning Revenant rules the Underscape with plasmatic power.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Razor</Owner><Name>Static Link</Name><Description>Creates a charged link between Razor and an enemy Hero, stealing damage from the target and giving it to Razor.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/razor_static_link_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 32/30/28/26</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/F8ZIMc-BLEo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Razor's polarity channels electricity into his being, draining the power of his opposition.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Razor</Owner><Name>Unstable Current</Name><Description>Razor moves with increased speed, and any abilities targeted at him are instantly countered with a jolt of electricity which damages, slows, and purges buffs from enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/razor_unstable_current_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/K2FcewK9HYQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Attacking the Lightning Revenant is rewarded with shock therapy.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Razor</Owner><Name>Eye of the Storm</Name><Description>A powerful lightning storm strikes out at enemy units with the lowest health, dealing damage and reducing their armor.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/razor_eye_of_the_storm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/150/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80/70/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/aMqqRjUH9g8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ride the lightning.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Riki</Owner><Name>Smoke Screen</Name><Description>Throws down a smoke bomb, silencing enemies, and causing them to miss most attacks, as well as slowing movement.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/riki_smoke_screen_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/s6qBkIfSEd4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Since his escape during the night of his betrayal, Riki has valued the use of a simple smoke screen to confuse his opponents.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Riki</Owner><Name>Blink Strike</Name><Description>Teleports behind the target unit, striking for bonus damage if it is an enemy.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/riki_blink_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/12/8/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fdacdcXVqYc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Stealth Assassin's agile movement makes him impossible to escape.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Riki</Owner><Name>Cloak and Dagger</Name><Description>Riki fades into the shadows, becoming invisible. Every time Riki strikes his enemy from behind, he deals bonus damage based on his Agility. When Riki attacks, he becomes visible.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/riki_permanent_invisibility_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Mtmn28XX-NM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Riki comes for you.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Riki</Owner><Name>Tricks of the Trade</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Phases out of the world while striking every enemy from behind in a 500 AoE once per second.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/riki_tricks_of_the_trade_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 40/35/30</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>The Stealth Assassin is not afraid to fight dirty, and specializes in attacking his opponents from behind.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Rubick</Owner><Name>Telekinesis</Name><Description>Rubick uses his telekinetic powers to lift the enemy into the air briefly and then hurls them back at the ground. The unit lands on the ground with such force that it stuns nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rubick_telekinesis_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/SbfekAl6ZBM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Even the Grandest Magus may use his powers for enjoyment.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Rubick</Owner><Name>Telekinesis Land</Name><Description>Chooses the location the target will land when Telekinesis finishes.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rubick_telekinesis_land_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZLrd3_57xKw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Rubick</Owner><Name>Fade Bolt</Name><Description>Rubick creates a powerful stream of arcane energy that travels between enemy units, dealing damage and reducing their attack damage.  Each jump deals less damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rubick_fade_bolt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/130/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/14/12/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/eZ6g4fnlkC8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Rubick's favorite spell for dispatching would-be assassins is a rather simple conjuration.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Rubick</Owner><Name>Null Field</Name><Description>Rubick's mastery of the arcane protects nearby allies against weaker magics, granting them magic resistance.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rubick_null_field_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/rGPFkEHi8QA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Not every magus can be a Grand Magus...</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Rubick</Owner><Name>Spell Steal</Name><Description>Rubick studies the trace magical essence of one enemy hero, learning the secrets of the last spell the hero cast. Rubick can use this spell as his own for several minutes or until he dies.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/rubick_spell_steal_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/18/16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RBiGEs77jDQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>...but even their lesser magics can be a source of much utility.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sand King</Owner><Name>Burrowstrike</Name><Description>Sand King burrows into the ground and tunnels forward, damaging and stunning enemy units above him as he resurfaces.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sandking_burrowstrike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 11</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BQNqhjqVtfg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Crixalis often lies in wait, burrowing under the surface to ambush his adversaries.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sand King</Owner><Name>Sand Storm</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Sand King creates a fearsome sandstorm that damages enemy units while hiding him from vision.  The invisibility remains for a short duration after the sandstorm ends.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sandking_sand_storm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/50/40/30</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 34/26/18/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/sUusCExNMHk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Some say Crixalis is a mirage; his carapace appearing then vanishing between the whirling sands of the Scintillant Waste.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sand King</Owner><Name>Caustic Finale</Name><Description>Sand King's attacks inject a venom that causes enemy units to violently explode when its timer expires, or when the unit dies, damaging and slowing nearby enemies. Deals 50% damage if its timer expires.

Caustic Finale is a Unique Attack Modifier, and does not stack with other Unique Attack Modifier.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sandking_caustic_finale_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HdesfveEum4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An injection from Crixalis makes one brittle and as dry as the arid wastes, subject to implosive demise.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sand King</Owner><Name>Epicenter</Name><Description>CHANNELED - After channeling for 2 seconds, Sand King sends a disturbance into the earth, causing it to shudder violently. All enemies caught within range will take damage and become slowed. Each subsequent pulse increases the radius of damage dealt.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sandking_epicenter_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/225/300</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120/110/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2_1y1pTdyIo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Many an explorer was lost to the quicksands of the Scintillant Waste.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Demon</Owner><Name>Disruption</Name><Description>Banishes the targeted unit from the battlefield for a short duration.  Upon returning, two illusions of the banished unit are created under Shadow Demon's control.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_demon_disruption_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25/22/19/16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/W2-DkeB2RiE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The pain of deception comes not while it happens, but when it is revealed.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Demon</Owner><Name>Soul Catcher</Name><Description>Curses a random enemy in an area to take increased damage.  Units under the effect of Disruption can still be affected by Soul Catcher.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_demon_soul_catcher_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/60/70/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13/12/11/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Yssy_fTDqGo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Trying to resist the Shadow Demon's corruption is mostly a useless endeavor.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Demon</Owner><Name>Shadow Poison</Name><Description>Deals damage in a line, and afflicts enemy units with a poison effect. The poison deals 1/2/4/8/16 times the stack damage based on the number of stacks on the target, up to 5 stacks. Additional stacks cause 50 damage each.  This deferred damage is dealt when Shadow Poison's duration is expired, or the Release sub-ability is used.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_demon_shadow_poison_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 2.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/XMIJwFcSAuM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The ever growing influence of the Shadow Demon can pollute the most valiant and pure of heroes.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Demon</Owner><Name>Shadow Poison Release</Name><Description>Releases the poison to do damage on all affected enemies. Units under the effect of Disruption can still be affected by Shadow Poison.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_demon_shadow_poison_release_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-v8vJdePA-k?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Demon</Owner><Name>Demonic Purge</Name><Description>Purges the target enemy unit, removing positive buffs, and slowing the target for the duration.  The unit slowly regains its speed until the end of the duration, upon which damage is dealt.  Units under the effect of Disruption can still be affected by Demonic Purge.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_demon_demonic_purge_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/200/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/nP4Hyx9hbjw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Once Shadow Demon no longer has any need for his collected cultist, he releases it from its subservience - and its life.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Fiend</Owner><Name>Shadowraze</Name><Description>Shadow Fiend razes the area in front of him, dealing damage to enemy units in an area.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nevermore_shadowraze1_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/NaBIR9oCECk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Nevermore's trademark for harvesting souls.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Fiend</Owner><Name>Necromastery</Name><Description>Shadow Fiend steals the soul from units he kills, gaining bonus damage. If the killed unit is a hero, he gains 12 souls.  On death, he releases half of them from bondage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nevermore_necromastery_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/CvNBpH08P5M?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Harvested souls swirl in and out of the Abysm, empowering the Shadow Fiend to increase the size of his collection.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Fiend</Owner><Name>Presence of the Dark Lord</Name><Description>Shadow Fiend's presence reduces the armor of nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nevermore_dark_lord_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/y3glSnq4mGQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Even being near Nevermore eats away at one's soul.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Fiend</Owner><Name>Requiem of Souls</Name><Description>Shadow Fiend gathers his captured souls to release them as lines of demonic energy. Units near Shadow Fiend when the souls are released can be damaged by several lines of energy. Any unit damaged by Requiem of Souls will have its movement speed and attack damage reduced. Lines of energy are created for every 2 souls captured through Necromastery. Requiem of Souls is automatically cast whenever Shadow Fiend dies, regardless of its cooldown.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/nevermore_requiem_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/175/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120/110/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/4kPz4cvIYEA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The captured souls of those past slain are released to ravage their former allies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Shaman</Owner><Name>Ether Shock</Name><Description>Creates a cone of ethereal energy that strikes multiple enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_shaman_ether_shock_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95/105/135/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/klelWIqMCVI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Originally used to open shows with the travelling con-man, Rhasta's lightning display shocks adversaries in more ways than one.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Shaman</Owner><Name>Hex</Name><Description>Transforms an enemy unit into a harmless creature, disabling their attacks and abilities.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_shaman_voodoo_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/140/170/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/QNp_Qa0FT5k?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Rhasta often ended performances by turning himself into a chicken - now, the humiliation is shared.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Shaman</Owner><Name>Shackles</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Magically binds an enemy unit so that it cannot move or attack, while dealing damage over time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_shaman_shackles_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 140/150/160/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Wu47XDHlzq0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A self-defense incantation, Rhasta developed shackles after his master was slain in the Bleeding Hills.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Shadow Shaman</Owner><Name>Mass Serpent Ward</Name><Description>Summons 10 Serpent Wards to attack enemy units and structures. The Wards are immune to magic, and have a small area of splash damage. It takes two hits to destroy a single Ward.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shadow_shaman_mass_serpent_ward_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/350/600</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/S64aSCeZUSY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Snake charming was a big part of the Shadow Shaman's act; now Rhasta can empower the snakes to do his bidding.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Silencer</Owner><Name>Arcane Curse</Name><Description>Curses the target area, causing enemy heroes to take damage and slowing their movement speed. Anytime affected enemies cast a spell, the duration is increased.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/silencer_curse_of_the_silent_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/95/115/135</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/18/16/14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1iiB545M6C0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Nortrom's lack of incantations is less of a problem for him than it is for his adversaries.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Silencer</Owner><Name>Glaives of Wisdom</Name><Description>Silencer enchants his glaives with his wisdom, dealing additional damage based on his Intelligence.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/silencer_glaives_of_wisdom_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 15/15/15/15</Mana><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/9-yINiC8IE4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Although lacking in traditional incantations, Nortrom's pedigree of the Aeol Drias gives him uncanny wisdom, which he applies to physical combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Silencer</Owner><Name>Last Word</Name><Description>Enchants a target, causing them to be damaged and silenced if they cast a spell or if the enchantment timer expires.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/silencer_last_word_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 115</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/24/18/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/VLHLahl4RDw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Nortrom ensures that spells uttered by his opponents will be their last.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Silencer</Owner><Name>Global Silence</Name><Description>Silencer stops all sound, preventing enemy heroes and units on the map from casting spells.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/silencer_global_silence_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 250/375/500</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 130</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/snCtUcpilzA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With a shock to the ground, all magic and sound pauses, and Nortrom fulfills his prophecy.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Skywrath Mage</Owner><Name>Arcane Bolt</Name><Description>Skywrath Mage launches a slow-moving bolt of arcane magic, dealing damage to an enemy unit based on Skywrath Mage's intelligence.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skywrath_mage_arcane_bolt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/70/70/70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5/4/3/2</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/TFjMorJ3PHU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Within the Ghastly Eyrie's endless intrigue, only the clever and calm can hope to survive.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Skywrath Mage</Owner><Name>Concussive Shot</Name><Description>Skywrath Mage sets off a long range shot that hits the closest hero within a long range.  Upon impact, it deals damage and slows in an area of effect.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skywrath_mage_concussive_shot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 18/16/14/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/tkF8HA5D5Sk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Those who serve the court of the Ghastly Eyrie are ever locked in covert war. One must always know where danger lurks nearest.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Skywrath Mage</Owner><Name>Ancient Seal</Name><Description>Skywrath Mage seals the targeted unit with an ancient rune, silencing it and causing it to take additional damage from spells.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skywrath_mage_ancient_seal_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/90/100/110</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/busbJBCRPho?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A holy incantation, whosoever finds themselves touched by Avilliva's sigil must suffer in penitent silence.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Skywrath Mage</Owner><Name>Mystic Flare</Name><Description>Skywrath Mage uses his ultimate magical ability to conjure a precise and violent mystical field that lays waste to his adversaries. Deals massive damage distributed evenly among any Heroes in the area over 2.4 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skywrath_mage_mystic_flare_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 350/575/800</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/40/20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/bCWXFPy8NYo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Only the most practiced of Skywrath sorcerers could hope to shape the skies into such a storm.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slardar</Owner><Name>Sprint</Name><Description>Slardar slithers ahead, moving significantly faster and passing through units, though becoming more vulnerable to damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slardar_sprint_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 17</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IIpt3UM9-dE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>As Slardar has made the transition from the Deeps, it has been necessary to use his powerful tail for sprinting instead of swimming.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slardar</Owner><Name>Slithereen Crush</Name><Description>Slams the ground, stunning and damaging nearby enemy land units.  After the stun, the affected units are slowed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slardar_slithereen_crush_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/95/105/115</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/AhBhn-UWcOM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A swift crush of might and water breaks even the toughest of defenses.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slardar</Owner><Name>Bash</Name><Description>Grants a chance that an attack will do bonus damage and stun an enemy.  The duration is doubled against creeps.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slardar_bash_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fxLD4HlBk8g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Thieves of the wealth of the Deep Ones meet the brutality of the Slithereen Guard in melee combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slardar</Owner><Name>Amplify Damage</Name><Description>Reduces enemy armor to amplify physical damage and provides True Sight of the targeted unit, revealing invisibility.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slardar_amplify_damage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wNlSGTlfxOY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Slardar's lure-light reveals even the most hidden of opponents, as well as their vulnerabilities.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slark</Owner><Name>Dark Pact</Name><Description>After a short delay, Slark sacrifices some of his life blood, purging most negative debuffs and dealing damage to enemy units around him and to himself.  Slark only takes 50% of the damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slark_dark_pact_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 55/50/45/40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 9/8/7/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OHGQ_BUhySI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Slithereen are capable of quickly regrowing appendages, in case of critical injury, to save their own lives.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slark</Owner><Name>Pounce</Name><Description>Slark leaps forward, grabbing the first hero he connects with.  That unit takes damage and is leashed to Slark, and can only move a limited distance away from Slark's landing position.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slark_pounce_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/16/12/8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/opGqZyhkBYw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Time in the Dark Reef made Slark a dangerous assassin; aggressive and fearless.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slark</Owner><Name>Essence Shift</Name><Description>Slark steals the life essence of enemy heroes with his attacks, draining each of their attributes and converting them to bonus Agility.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slark_essence_shift_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/60HPDokFuvU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With each strike at his adversaries, Slark's knowledge of their weaknesses improves.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Slark</Owner><Name>Shadow Dance</Name><Description>When used, Slark hides himself in a cloud of shadows, becoming immune to detection. Attacking, casting spells, and using items will not reveal Slark.  Passively, when not visible to the enemy team, Slark gains bonus movement speed and health regeneration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/slark_shadow_dance_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/k8jpsm0VhGk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The hidden Thirteenth is a slippery foe.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sniper</Owner><Name>Shrapnel</Name><Description>Consumes a charge to launch a ball of shrapnel that showers the target area in explosive pellets. Enemies are subject to damage and slowed movement. Reveals the targeted area. Shrapnel charges restore every 55 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sniper_shrapnel_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZQuwiZ4LErM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Kardel's modular rifle also fires incendiary rounds, useful for assaulting entrenched locations.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sniper</Owner><Name>Headshot</Name><Description>Sniper increases his accuracy, giving him a chance to deal extra damage and briefly stop the movements of his enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sniper_headshot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/xwArHJFxywE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Taking potshots at steepstalkers in his childhood has been thoroughly refined into perfect leads on enemy combatants.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sniper</Owner><Name>Take Aim</Name><Description>Extends the attack range of Sniper's rifle.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sniper_take_aim_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZehVtSyXDaE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Kardel always takes it upon himself to stay as far from harm as he can while still performing his role - taking perfect aim.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sniper</Owner><Name>Assassinate</Name><Description>Sniper locks onto a target enemy unit and, after 2 seconds, fires a devastating shot that deals damage at long range, and mini-stuns the target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sniper_assassinate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 175/275/375</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/15/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Ghp0_Dnk05A?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In order to fulfill the prophecy and return to his home town, Kardel must make another shot as perfect as the one on the day of his ancient test.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spectre</Owner><Name>Spectral Dagger</Name><Description>Spectre flings a dagger to draw a Shadow Path, dealing damage and slowing the movement speed of any enemies along the trail. Units hit by the dagger also trail a Shadow Path. While treading the path, Spectre phases through otherwise impassable terrain.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spectre_spectral_dagger_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 130/140/150/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HqPfci6NzAc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Mercurial's dagger eclipses the physical plane in shadow, a state in which mortals cower, but spectres thrive.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spectre</Owner><Name>Desolate</Name><Description>Deals bonus damage whenever Spectre attacks an enemy who is alone.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spectre_desolate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/kFwX40wvYbs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Often times, warriors find themselves alone with a vision of Mercurial - the fated question is if it is the true Spectre.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spectre</Owner><Name>Dispersion</Name><Description>Damage done to Spectre is reflected on her enemies, leaving her unharmed. The effect lessens with distance.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spectre_dispersion_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/r-jRKC2Vhhw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A daunting task lies before enemies of Mercurial - killing a shadow with blade and magic.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spectre</Owner><Name>Reality</Name><Description>Spectre exchanges places with a chosen Haunt.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spectre_reality_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/A4bKLBRVo8U?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The scattered shadows unite into the one true Spectre.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spectre</Owner><Name>Haunt</Name><Description>Creates a spectral nemesis to attack each enemy hero after a short delay. At any moment during the duration, Spectre can use Reality to exchange places of a given haunt.

Haunt illusions are uncontrollable, take extra damage, and deal less damage than Spectre herself.  They move at 400 base movement speed and ignore terrain.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spectre_haunt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/150/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140/130/120</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wI0WOL1XEj4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>At the height of combat, Mercurial's physical manifestation shatters, and the shadowy pieces haunt those who still cling to life.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spirit Breaker</Owner><Name>Charge of Darkness</Name><Description>Spirit Breaker fixes his sight on an enemy unit and starts charging through all objects.  All enemy units passed through and the targeted unit will be hit by a Greater Bash.  If the targeted unit dies, Spirit Breaker will change his target to the nearest enemy unit to that location.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spirit_breaker_charge_of_darkness_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/agoz4rtoSIw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Barathrum erupts from the darkness with unwieldy force.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spirit Breaker</Owner><Name>Empowering Haste</Name><Description>Causes Spirit Breaker to gain power with higher movement speed. His presence increases the movement speed of nearby allied units. Can be cast to improve the movement speed bonus for 6 seconds, however afterward the passive bonus will be halved while the ability is on cooldown.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spirit_breaker_empowering_haste_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OzdXb3TQfy0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Aspiring heroes gain speed and power from simply observing the Spirit Breaker's dominance on the battle field.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spirit Breaker</Owner><Name>Greater Bash</Name><Description>Gives a chance to stun and knockback an enemy unit on an attack, as well as gaining bonus movement speed after a bash occurs. Deals a percentage of movement speed as damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spirit_breaker_greater_bash_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-GTN7_EjR7A?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The signature strike of Barathrum's ghostly ball and chain.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Spirit Breaker</Owner><Name>Nether Strike</Name><Description>Spirit Breaker slips into the nether realm, reappearing next to his hapless victim. Upon reappearing, a Greater Bash of the current level occurs and deals bonus damage.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/spirit_breaker_nether_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/150/175</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80/70/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OGmmniz9Oeo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Barathrum temporarily returns to the realm from where he came, bringing with him the retribution of both worlds.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Storm Spirit</Owner><Name>Static Remnant</Name><Description>Creates an explosively charged image of Storm Spirit that lasts 12 seconds and will detonate and deal damage if an enemy unit comes near it.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/storm_spirit_static_remnant_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 3.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/MZaI7VTnH4M?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Raijin Thunderkeg's duality allows him to admire himself in shocking fashion.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Storm Spirit</Owner><Name>Electric Vortex</Name><Description>A vortex that pulls an enemy unit to Storm Spirit's location, it also slows the Storm Spirit by 50% for 3 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/storm_spirit_electric_vortex_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 85</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 21/20/19/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/8oThvhyYgDk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Raijin's thunderous, boisterous energy often draws others into an electrifying situation.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Storm Spirit</Owner><Name>Overload</Name><Description>Casting a spell creates an electrical charge, which is released in a burst on his next attack, dealing damage and slowing nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/storm_spirit_overload_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/og2EaLlgRzI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Pow!  Zip!  Zap!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Storm Spirit</Owner><Name>Ball Lightning</Name><Description>Storm Spirit becomes volatile electricity, charging across the battlefield until he depletes his mana or reaches his target. The activation mana cost is 30+8% of his total mana pool, and the cost per 100 units traveled is 12+0.7% of his total mana pool.  Damage is expressed in damage per 100 units traveled.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/storm_spirit_ball_lightning_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 30</Mana><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Km-2rbf6qcs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Storm is coming in.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sven</Owner><Name>Storm Hammer</Name><Description>Sven unleashes his magical gauntlet that deals damage and stuns enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sven_storm_bolt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-BNx6j67GMM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Rogue Knight's iron gauntlet, taken from the school of his father, strikes his foes to their core.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sven</Owner><Name>Great Cleave</Name><Description>Sven strikes with great force, cleaving all nearby enemy units with his attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sven_great_cleave_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/XRI-eUBr_S8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Vigil Knights still seek to reclaim the stolen Outcast Blade from Sven, a weapon capable of cutting wide swaths through lesser warriors.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sven</Owner><Name>Warcry</Name><Description>Sven's Warcry heartens his allies for battle, increasing their movement speed and armor.  Lasts 8 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sven_warcry_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 25/25/25/25</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 32/26/20/14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/npLme9BdTy8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Calling a few lines from the Vigil Codex fortifies Sven's obedience to his rogue code. So poetic!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Sven</Owner><Name>God's Strength</Name><Description>Sven channels his rogue strength, granting bonus damage for 25 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/sven_gods_strength_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/150/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/EbnTUOTMvkg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>With the strength that shattered the Sacred Helm, the Rogue Knight stands unopposed in melee combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Techies</Owner><Name>Land Mines</Name><Description>Plant an invisible mine that explodes when an enemy steps near.  The explosion will deal less damage if the enemy is farther away from the mine when it explodes.  Mines explode 0.3 seconds after being triggered.  Damages buildings.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/techies_land_mines_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/75/85/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 9/8/7/5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2CE4VAX29Bo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The bane of Toterin!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Techies</Owner><Name>Stasis Trap</Name><Description>Plant an invisible trap that stuns nearby enemy units when triggered.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/techies_stasis_trap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/110/140/160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/16/13/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/mkoWUQ2JTQA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The scourge of Trapper Town!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Techies</Owner><Name>Suicide Squad, Attack!</Name><Description>Techies sacrifice themselves for the greater good, dealing massive area of effect damage.  More damage is dealt to units closer to Techies when they explode.  Techies' respawn time is reduced by 50% when killed by this ability.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/techies_suicide_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/125/150/175</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 160/140/120/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/yieLNvs_GPc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>What's this button do?</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Techies</Owner><Name>Focused Detonate</Name><Description>Detonate all remote mines in the target area.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/techies_focused_detonate_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Why light one fuse when you can light them all?</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Techies</Owner><Name>Minefield Sign</Name><Description>Plant a warning sign to remind enemies to step lightly. Only one sign can exist at a time. Lasts 180 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/techies_minefield_sign_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 360</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/pc5c9hep9ZQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Watch your step!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Techies</Owner><Name>Remote Mines</Name><Description>Plant an invisible explosive that will only detonate when triggered.  Does not damage buildings.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/techies_remote_mines_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/240/300</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/MtWbyUgaAZA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The downfall of Dredger's Bight!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Templar Assassin</Owner><Name>Refraction</Name><Description>Templar Assassin becomes highly elusive, avoiding damage and gaining a bonus to her damage.  The damage and avoidance effects are separate, and have a limited number of instances.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/templar_assassin_refraction_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 17</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/xrj3rk70xrs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Manipulating her psionic veil, Lanaya bends nature's law to her will.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Templar Assassin</Owner><Name>Meld</Name><Description>Templar Assassin conceals herself, becoming invisible as long as she remains still.  If Meld's invisibility is broken by attacking an enemy, Lanaya will deal bonus damage to the enemy and reduce their armor for 10 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/templar_assassin_meld_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-oa6PPpOtiM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lanaya is as elusive as her covenant with the Hidden Temple.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Templar Assassin</Owner><Name>Psi Blades</Name><Description>Templar Assassin's psi blades slice through the attacked unit, splitting and damaging enemy units directly behind it, while gaining bonus attack range.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/templar_assassin_psi_blades_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/TujHkI7r5Lw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Her blades pierce the skin as much as the mind, furthering her understanding of the mystery that is reality.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Templar Assassin</Owner><Name>Trap</Name><Description>Springs the nearest trap, slowing nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/templar_assassin_trap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0.50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/kZkWoqTLTrY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Templar Assassin</Owner><Name>Psionic Trap</Name><Description>Templar Assassin places mystical traps that invisibly monitor enemy movement. When sprung at her command, they exert a slowing influence of 30% in the area. Traps charge up to slow an additional 5% every second, up to 50%.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/templar_assassin_psionic_trap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 15/15/15</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 11/8/5</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Calling upon the reach of the Hidden Temple, none escape the eye of the Templar.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Terrorblade</Owner><Name>Reflection</Name><Description>Terrorblade brings forth an invulnerable dark reflection of all nearby enemy heroes. Affected enemy heroes are slowed and attacked by their reflection.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/terrorblade_reflection_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 22/20/18/16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/fuym8gNLAr0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the fractal prison of Foulfell, Terrorblade learned the truth of this old tale: you are your own worst enemy.  Now it is a lesson he teaches others.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Terrorblade</Owner><Name>Conjure Image</Name><Description>Creates an illusion of Terrorblade that deals damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/terrorblade_conjure_image_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/-b0yMS7uu2g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>There's only one thing more dangerous than facing Terrorblade.  Facing MORE Terrrorblades!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Terrorblade</Owner><Name>Metamorphosis</Name><Description>Terrorblade transforms into a powerful demon with a ranged attack. Any of Terrorblade's illusions that are within 900 range will also be transformed by Metamorphosis.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/terrorblade_metamorphosis_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/nGq0lqaBngU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Temper, temper. The rage rises up and takes control.  Meet Terrorblade's own worst self.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Terrorblade</Owner><Name>Sunder</Name><Description>Severs the life from both Terrorblade and a target hero, exchanging a percentage of both units' current health. Some health points must remain.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/terrorblade_sunder_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/100/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 120/80/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/_r-fKYPSnlw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>You didn't need that life, did you?  The demon marauder steals that which you hold most dear.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tidehunter</Owner><Name>Gush</Name><Description>Summons a gush of water to damage an enemy unit, reducing their movement speed and armor.  Lasts 4 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tidehunter_gush_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/68728IYAiok?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>During his championship of the Sunken Isles, Leviathan gained mastery over the open sea.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tidehunter</Owner><Name>Kraken Shell</Name><Description>Thickens Tidehunter's hide to passively block a portion of any incoming physical attack damage. The hide also removes negative status effects if the damage taken crosses a threshold.

Does not stack with items that provide Damage Block.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tidehunter_kraken_shell_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/mbIfRCkRM6g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Claddish navymen tell tales of a mighty sea-faring beast that suffered spear and sword but continued to lay waste to the fleet.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tidehunter</Owner><Name>Anchor Smash</Name><Description>Tidehunter swings his mighty anchor to damage nearby enemies and reduce their attack damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tidehunter_anchor_smash_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 30/40/50/60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 7/6/5/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/30uJcLr3ttA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Stolen from one of Admiral Kunkka's flagships, Leviathan's heavy anchor proves useful as a melee weapon.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tidehunter</Owner><Name>Ravage</Name><Description>Slams the ground, causing tentacles to erupt in all directions, damaging and stunning all nearby enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tidehunter_ravage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/225/325</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 150</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/BZBsiD9wuWQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Calling to the abyssal god Maelrawn has resulted in entire armadas being lost at sea.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Whirling Death</Name><Description>Timbersaw whirls extremely sharp edges, damaging enemies and destroying trees around him in an area.  If an enemy hero is affected, it loses some of its primary attribute for a short duration.  Whirling Death will deal Pure damage if a tree is cut down in the process.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_whirling_death_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Lx4tosarCHM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the case that Rizzrack gets surrounded by the the vines and plants of his nightmares, he has an immediate chainsaw defense.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Timber Chain</Name><Description>Timbersaw fires a chain that embeds itself in the first tree it hits, pulling him towards it.  Any enemy in the path takes damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_timber_chain_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/70/80/90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/v2G3fSQXZwA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>You never know when you might need to escape from malevolent saplings.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Reactive Armor</Name><Description>Each time Timbersaw is attacked, he gains increased health regen and armor.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_reactive_armor_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IU_H0tbuK1Q?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The saw-suit is equipped to react to the slightest touch with fortified defenses.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Chakram</Name><Description>Fires a secondary saw blade at the target location where it will spin in place, dealing damage in an area around it.  Additionally, for each 5% of health missing, enemies caught in the saw blade move more slowly. The blade deals damage and cuts down trees in its path when fired and retracted.  While active the ability costs mana, and you lose the ability to attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_chakram_2_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/150/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>Cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut cut!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Return Chakram</Name><Description>Returns the Chakram to Timbersaw.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_return_chakram_2_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Chakram</Name><Description>Fires your main saw blade at the target location where it will spin in place, dealing damage in an area around it.  Enemies caught in the saw blade will move more slowly for every 5% of health missing. The blade deals damage and cuts down trees in its path when fired and retracted.  While active the ability costs mana, and you lose the ability to attack.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_chakram_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/150/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/a3uWkquhsaE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The ultimate in anti-flora weaponry.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Timbersaw</Owner><Name>Return Chakram</Name><Description>Returns the Chakram to Timbersaw.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/shredder_return_chakram_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video /><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tinker</Owner><Name>Laser</Name><Description>Fires an intense energy beam, dealing damage and blinding the target, causing it to miss all physical attacks. 

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tinker_laser_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 95/120/145/170</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/2tDx6grjLns?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Boush perfected this rock cutting laser in his subterranean laboratory, never considering its combat utility.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tinker</Owner><Name>Heat-Seeking Missile</Name><Description>Launches a pair of rockets at the nearest visible enemy heroes within 2500 range. 

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tinker_heat_seeking_missile_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/140/160/180</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jK4Sn_EDBpE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The last contraption Boush was able to save was a retrofitted rocket launcher with a homing mechanism.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tinker</Owner><Name>March of the Machines</Name><Description>Enlists an army of robotic minions to destroy enemy units in an area around Tinker.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tinker_march_of_the_machines_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 145/150/165/190</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/AmXRvkaYhIE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Even though the laboratory has since been sealed off, the ability to radio in robotic drones is still in working order.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tinker</Owner><Name>Rearm</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Resets the cooldown on most of Tinker's items and abilities.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tinker_rearm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/200/300</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/eHlwkFnGtzs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A new battery here, another set of rockets there, Boush continually improves on existing technology.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tiny</Owner><Name>Avalanche</Name><Description>Bombards an area with rocks, stunning and damaging enemy land units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tiny_avalanche_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 17</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/t4JvtlBfJug?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Inanimate rock becomes animate when called by the Stone Giant.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tiny</Owner><Name>Toss</Name><Description>Grabs the nearest unit in a 275 radius around Tiny, ally or enemy, and launches it at the target unit or rune to deal damage where they land.  If the tossed unit is an enemy, it will take an extra 20% damage. Toss does more damage with each level in Grow.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tiny_toss_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/4oDiWbybHgM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Tiny's gargantuan stature allows him to catapult even the sturdiest of warriors.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tiny</Owner><Name>Craggy Exterior</Name><Description>Causes damage to bounce back on Tiny's attackers.  Enemies that attack Tiny from within 300 units have a chance of being stunned.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tiny_craggy_exterior_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/P0uPxATF8XE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Melee warriors tend to find attacking the Stone Giant largely ineffective.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tiny</Owner><Name>Grow</Name><Description>Tiny gains craggy mass that increases his power at the cost of his attack speed. Increases Tossed unit damage and improves movement speed.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tiny_grow_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/4GB3qojLOHo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Watching a hill become a mountain is awe-inspiring - especially if the mountain begins laying waste to adversaries.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Treant Protector</Owner><Name>Nature's Guise</Name><Description>Causes the targeted unit to blend in with the forest, becoming invisible to enemies and gaining a movement speed bonus when near a tree.  If the unit moves away from a tree or the spell is cast on a unit with no nearby trees, Nature's Guise is lost.  Treant Protector can cast spells and remain invisible under Nature's Guise.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/treant_natures_guise_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10/8/6/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RrG1oa36SLk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Protectors don't often come into vision; their natural state being nestled within their leafy brethren.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Treant Protector</Owner><Name>Leech Seed</Name><Description>Treant plants a life-sapping seed in an enemy unit, draining its health, while simultaneously slowing it. The seed heals friendly units around it.  Pulses 6 times.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/treant_leech_seed_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 80/95/110/125</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/13/10/7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/DxUAavLdUNM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Rooftrellen nurtures the beings under his stewardship, sustained by the lifeforce of trespassers into his sacred ground.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Treant Protector</Owner><Name>Living Armor</Name><Description>Infuses the target hero or structure with a protective coating which grants bonus regeneration. Also blocks some damage from all sources. Dispels when a number of damage instances are taken.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/treant_living_armor_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30/24/18/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/DkpjC57bU_g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The roots and tendrils of the Treant Protectors are far-reaching, stimulating the growth and rejuvenation of all of nature.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Treant Protector</Owner><Name>Eyes In The Forest</Name><Description>Treant Protector enchants a tree, which grants him unobstructed vision in that location. If Overgrowth is cast, units within a radius of an enchanted tree will be entangled and damaged.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/treant_eyes_in_the_forest_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 25</Cooldown><Video /><Lore>One can never be too certain who, or what, might need protecting.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Treant Protector</Owner><Name>Overgrowth</Name><Description>Summons an overgrowth of vines and branches around Treant that prevent afflicted enemies from moving, blinking, going invisible, or attacking.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/treant_overgrowth_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/175/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Sz6oCVgEAIY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Rooftrellen calls the ancestral spirit of nature, releasing its power through all of his kin.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Troll Warlord</Owner><Name>Berserker's Rage</Name><Description>While active, Troll Warlord swaps from using ranged to melee attacks. Melee attacks have a chance to bash, dealing bonus damage and stunning the target. Berserker's Rage also grants additional health, movement speed, armor, and increased attack speed.

Whirling Axes has different functionality while Berserker's Rage is active.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/troll_warlord_berserkers_rage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5hm9QkwMsuk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Like his anger, Troll Warlord's supply of axes is infinite.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Troll Warlord</Owner><Name>Whirling Axes (Ranged)</Name><Description>Troll hurls a fistful of five axes in a cone shape over 900 range, slowing and damaging enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/troll_warlord_whirling_axes_ranged_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 19/16/13/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/pqe5QcZDAEE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Only axes fueled by hate whirl with such a deadly spin.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Troll Warlord</Owner><Name>Whirling Axes (Melee)</Name><Description>Troll hurls two axes around him in a close range area of effect, damaging enemy units and causing them to miss some attacks.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/troll_warlord_whirling_axes_melee_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/50/50/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/x9u8gk8vczg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Keep your enemies close.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Troll Warlord</Owner><Name>Fervor</Name><Description>With each continuous blow on the same target, Troll gains increased attack speed.  If Troll changes targets, the stacks drop to zero.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/troll_warlord_fervor_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Ba5LZHZaAts?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>If at first you don't succeed, strike, strike again.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Troll Warlord</Owner><Name>Battle Trance</Name><Description>Troll's presence on the battlefield increases the attack speed of himself and all allied heroes.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/troll_warlord_battle_trance_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/YLDwkaESv9U?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An adrenaline rush of pure hatred quickens your blades.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tusk</Owner><Name>Ice Shards</Name><Description>Tusk compresses shards of ice into a ball of frozen energy that damages all enemies it comes in contact with. When the ball reaches its target destination the shards are released, creating a barrier that lasts for 7 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tusk_ice_shards_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/105/110/115</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 19/16/13/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/b0hv_O6t8PI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the frozen tundra near the Barrier, after the last sun of autumn has set, ice can form with alarming speed.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tusk</Owner><Name>Snowball</Name><Description>Tusk begins rolling into a snowball. Allies within a 350 radius can also be added to the snowball by right-clicking on them, even while the snowball is moving. Once launched, any enemies caught in the snowball's path will be stunned and take damage. Each allied Hero in the snowball will add to its damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tusk_snowball_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 21/20/19/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/ZHvQHTdctGk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Tales are still told of the wild feat that ended the grand brawl at White Fields.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tusk</Owner><Name>Frozen Sigil</Name><Description>Tusk summons a Frozen Sigil by calling upon the deepest cold of winter. The Sigil creates a snowstorm which slows all enemy units within 600 range.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tusk_frozen_sigil_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/emCjRsmIMKg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The chill of home!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tusk</Owner><Name>Launch Snowball</Name><Description>Launch the snowball toward the target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tusk_launch_snowball_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video /><Lore>Into the great wide white!</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tusk</Owner><Name>Walrus Kick</Name><Description>Kicks the target unit back, damaging them and slowing their movement speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tusk_walrus_kick_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/5lLGX4Vyg7A?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore /></Skill><Skill><Owner>Tusk</Owner><Name>Walrus PUNCH!</Name><Description>Tusk connects with his mighty Walrus Punch, a critical strike so powerful it launches its victim into the air. The victim is slowed upon landing.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/tusk_walrus_punch_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 50/75/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 36/24/12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wOQx_jM-dcE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It never matters who throws the first punch, only who throws the last.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Undying</Owner><Name>Decay</Name><Description>Undying steals strength from all enemy heroes in an area, dealing base damage as he claims the enemy's strength for himself.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/undying_decay_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/90/110/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10/8/6/4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/oiPPDIIyLF4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The strength of the living is simply borrowed from the strength of the dead.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Undying</Owner><Name>Soul Rip</Name><Description>Undying rips health away from all nearby units and uses it to heal an ally, or damage an enemy. Soul Rip can also be used to heal Tombstone.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/undying_soul_rip_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/110/120/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24/18/12/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/8NDBna9Mi1E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Even allies feel despair in Undying's presence.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Undying</Owner><Name>Tombstone</Name><Description>Summons a tombstone at the target point.  Zombies will frequently spawn next to every enemy unit in the area around the Tombstone, and attack them.  Zombies have the Deathlust ability, which causes their attacks to slow the target, and if the target reaches below a certain amount of health, increases the attack and movement speed of the zombie.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/undying_tombstone_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/130/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/hb931I8cwiM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Dirge calls on his fallen brothers to fight for the Dead God.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Undying</Owner><Name>Flesh Golem</Name><Description>Undying transforms into a horrifying flesh golem that possesses a Plague Aura.  This aura slows all enemy units within 750 range and amplifies the damage they take; the closer to Undying, the more damage and slow.  When a plagued unit dies, Undying is healed equal to a percentage of his own maximum health.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/undying_flesh_golem_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 75</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/pfTqhK3DWsc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The flesh of the recently dead add to the power of Dirge's plague.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ursa</Owner><Name>Earthshock</Name><Description>Ursa slams the earth, causing a powerful shock to damage and slow all enemy units in a nearby area for 4 seconds.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ursa_earthshock_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uF9RW4aDK-I?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The very steps of a male ursine shake the ground as well as the resolve of opposing warriors.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ursa</Owner><Name>Overpower</Name><Description>Using his skill in combat, Ursa gains increased attack speed for a number of subsequent attacks.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ursa_overpower_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 45/55/65/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/HnjRrXrXoVo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>For a behemoth of his size, Ursa is deceptively nimble.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ursa</Owner><Name>Fury Swipes</Name><Description>Ursa's claws dig deeper wounds in the enemy, causing consecutive attacks to the same enemy to deal more damage.  If the same target is not attacked after 15 seconds, the bonus damage is lost.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ursa_fury_swipes_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Ehq2ElYhdls?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In nature, the wounded rarely survive the attacks of hungry predators.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Ursa</Owner><Name>Enrage</Name><Description>Ursa goes into a frenzy, multiplying his Fury Swipes damage and causing him to take 80% less damage. Removes any existing debuffs.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/ursa_enrage_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 0/0/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50/40/30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/eZf3Yz_BAbk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ulfsaar succumbs to his ancient spirit, becoming the most ferocious creature on the battlefield.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Vengeful Spirit</Owner><Name>Magic Missile</Name><Description>Fires a magic missile at an enemy unit, stunning and dealing damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/vengefulspirit_magic_missile_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 13/12/11/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/v0QcCg9lEzU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A simple Skywrath technique, the magic missile is Shendel's primary tool for vengeance.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Vengeful Spirit</Owner><Name>Wave of Terror</Name><Description>Vengeful Spirit lets loose a wicked cry, weakening the armor of enemies and giving vision of the path ahead.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/vengefulspirit_wave_of_terror_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 40/40/40/40</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/M-40xlCUWac?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Shendel's haunting voice hints at her approaching vindication.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Vengeful Spirit</Owner><Name>Vengeance Aura</Name><Description>Vengeful Spirit's presence increases the physical damage of nearby friendly units. If Vengeful Spirit is slain, her killer will be possessed with a negative Vengeance Aura, reducing the damage of her killer and its nearby allies until Vengeful Spirit revives.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/vengefulspirit_command_aura_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/313ljmCbIiQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Although they may not share her undying passion for revenge, allies do draw on her fanaticism in combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Vengeful Spirit</Owner><Name>Nether Swap</Name><Description>Instantaneously swaps positions with a target Hero, friend or enemy.  Nether Swap interrupts channeling abilities on the target.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/vengefulspirit_nether_swap_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/150/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 45</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/MSS_SNkHVEo?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Martyrdom is a small price to pay for vengeance.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Venomancer</Owner><Name>Venomous Gale</Name><Description>Launches a ball of venom in a line, poisoning enemy units so that they take both initial damage and damage over time, as well as suffering slowed movement.  Venomous Gale deals damage every 3 seconds over its duration.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/venomancer_venomous_gale_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 21/20/19/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/NMl5uOEHfCM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A concoction of various stings, poisons, and toxins gathered from the jungles of Jidi Isle, victims surviving it are rare.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Venomancer</Owner><Name>Poison Sting</Name><Description>Adds poison damage to Venomancer's normal attacks, slowing movement speed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/venomancer_poison_sting_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/wHPx7hm2j8w?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The paralytic sting of the creature which caused his transformation now belongs to the Venomancer.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Venomancer</Owner><Name>Plague Ward</Name><Description>Summons a plague ward to attack enemy units and structures. The ward is immune to magic. Wards gain the Poison Sting level from Venomancer, dealing 50% of the full damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/venomancer_plague_ward_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 20/20/20/20</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 5</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/vQ0AFxdBUwk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A mixture of his old herbalist talents and newfound toxic mastery creates a living embodiment of plague.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Venomancer</Owner><Name>Poison Nova</Name><Description>A spreading ring of poison that does damage over time to enemy units around Venomancer.  Poison Nova cannot deal lethal damage; targets will be left with at least 1 health.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/venomancer_poison_nova_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/300/400</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 140/120/100</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/gL3GCUp1Ins?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>In the Acid Jungles, creatures releasing noxious poison to their attackers is common; Venomancer spreads this plague beyond the Jidi Isle.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Viper</Owner><Name>Poison Attack</Name><Description>Intensifies Viper's venom, adding an effect to his normal attack that slows attack and movement speed while dealing damage over time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/viper_poison_attack_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 20/20/20/20</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/FWLMTu44daQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Netherdrake's inborn toxic breath quickly drains the vitality of its afflicted.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Viper</Owner><Name>Nethertoxin</Name><Description>Nethertoxin causes Viper's normal attack to deal bonus damage to units based on how much health they are missing.  The bonus damage doubles for each 20% of health missing from the target.  Nethertoxin deals half damage to creeps and buildings.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/viper_nethertoxin_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/OH2fLJO993U?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Poison from the Nether Reaches turns wounds into fatalities, and fatigue into death.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Viper</Owner><Name>Corrosive Skin</Name><Description>Viper exudes an infectious toxin that damages and slows any enemy that damages it in a 1400 radius. The acid exudate also increases Viper's resistance to magic.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/viper_corrosive_skin_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/RGDVz0J6g2g?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>It is not unusual for sword and shield alike to corrode in the very hands of those who attack the Netherdrake.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Viper</Owner><Name>Viper Strike</Name><Description>Viper slows the targeted enemy unit's movement and attack speed while also dealing poison damage over time.  The slowing effect reduces over the duration of the poison.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/viper_viper_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 125/175/250</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 70/50/30</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/109y0icISWw?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Once used to slay his sadistic summoner, the most powerful of Netherdrake infections spreads through the veins of those foolish enough to cross Viper.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Visage</Owner><Name>Grave Chill</Name><Description>Visage drains the movement and attack speed of the targeted unit, gaining it for itself.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/visage_grave_chill_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16/14/12/10</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/Wn_IpUEFnOk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The warmth of the sun is never felt in the dark cold of the Narrow Maze.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Visage</Owner><Name>Soul Assumption</Name><Description>Visage gathers charges of soul essence each time nearby heroes take more than 110 damage. When the essence is released, it deals base damage as well as damage for each gathered soul charge.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/visage_soul_assumption_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 170/160/150/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 4</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/NCV_P7rUw-8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The collected souls of the dead reach out to bring another into their fold.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Visage</Owner><Name>Gravekeeper's Cloak</Name><Description>Visage generates a layered barrier that protects him from physical and magical attacks.  If he receives damage from a player, one layer is removed, and takes time to recover.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/visage_gravekeepers_cloak_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jAG74Ac-Z4o?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Visage's tough scales share equal properties of ghost and stone, making it nearly impervious to blade and magical assault.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Visage</Owner><Name>Summon Familiars</Name><Description>Conjures two blind Familiars to fight for Visage.  Familiars have high attack power, but each attack drains a charge of damage that recharges slowly over time.  Familiars possess the Stone Form ability, that allows them to turn into stone, stunning enemies upon landing.  While in Stone Form, Familiars are invulnerable, and rapidly regenerate their health and damage.  Familiars grant high bounty when killed.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/visage_summon_familiars_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/150/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 180/160/140</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/_wBf8zfMfFc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Guardians of the Narrow Maze, Necro'lic's Familiars stand watch over his domain.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Warlock</Owner><Name>Fatal Bonds</Name><Description>Binds several enemy units together, causing 25% of the damage dealt to one of them to be felt by the others.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/warlock_fatal_bonds_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/120/120/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24/22/20/18</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uRFLMNzJ7Vs?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>An ancient incantation that links the vital energies of multiple lifeforms into one collective body.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Warlock</Owner><Name>Shadow Word</Name><Description>Warlock whispers an incantation, healing a friendly unit or damaging an enemy unit over time.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/warlock_shadow_word_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/110/130/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 16</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/1ExGT5E8-FE?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Demnok's arcane arts have a myriad of uses, allowing them to be powerful friendly enchantments or damaging curses.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Warlock</Owner><Name>Upheaval</Name><Description>CHANNELED - A powerful slowing current that grows stronger as it's channelled. Lasts up to 16 seconds.  Enemies are slowed for 3 seconds after leaving the area or the spell ends.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/warlock_upheaval_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/110/120/130</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50/46/42/38</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/9VHxyxOkHek?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Demnok manipulates space-time, impairing entire armies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Warlock</Owner><Name>Chaotic Offering</Name><Description>Summons a Golem from the depths, stunning enemies for one second. The Golem lives 60 seconds, takes reduced damage from spells, has Permanent Immolation and Flaming Fists on attack.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/warlock_rain_of_chaos_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/300/400</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 165</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/LlUYOShkrE0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Demnok unleashes the captive spirit in his Dreadwood staff, causing destruction in enemy ranks.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Weaver</Owner><Name>The Swarm</Name><Description>Weaver launches a swarm of 12 young Weavers that latch on any enemy unit in their path, attacking and reducing armor until it is killed.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/weaver_the_swarm_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 70/80/90/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 35/30/25/20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/YfngG2WLpfc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Skitskurr opens a gap in the space time fabric, allowing young Weavers to slip through and aid him in combat.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Weaver</Owner><Name>Shukuchi</Name><Description>Weaver shifts out of visibility, gaining the ability to move at maximum speed through physical units--doing harm to any enemies it passes through.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/weaver_shukuchi_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 60/60/60/60</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12/10/8/6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/d5tRF1b5L5E?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>As the Weavers worked in the fabric of creation, small wormholes allowed them to slip through time to better work their craft.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Weaver</Owner><Name>Geminate Attack</Name><Description>Allows Weaver to dispatch two attacks at once.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/weaver_geminate_attack_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6/5/4/3</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/UGW_dID1W5c?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Skitskurr's relationship with time is somewhat variable, causing his actions to be witnessed - and felt - more than once.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Weaver</Owner><Name>Time Lapse</Name><Description>Weaver warps backward to whatever position it was in five seconds earlier--regaining the HP and mana from that time. No effect on cooldown, gold or experience.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/weaver_time_lapse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 150/75/0</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60/50/40</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cmgRjaiscEg?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>If Skitskurr does not deem the current reality of the world to fit his desires, he simply crawls back in time to right what was wronged.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Windranger</Owner><Name>Shackleshot</Name><Description>Shackles the target to an enemy unit or tree in a line directly behind it.  If no unit or tree is present, the stun duration is reduced to 0.75.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/windrunner_shackleshot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 12</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/NZEnx0l_zJ0?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Windranger's variety of bow skills includes an arrow with thick ropes attached to encumber any escaping target.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Windranger</Owner><Name>Powershot</Name><Description>Windranger charges her bow for up to 1 second for a single powerful shot, which deals more damage the longer it is charged. The arrow damages enemies and destroys trees along its path. For each enemy that Powershot hits, its damage is reduced by 10%.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/windrunner_powershot_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 90/100/110/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 9</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/dBHEtbYmask?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>During her early years of training, Lyralei learned to fire powerful arrows that cleaved even trees to reach their targets.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Windranger</Owner><Name>Windrun</Name><Description>Increases movement speed and adds evasion from all physical attacks, while slowing movement of nearby enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/windrunner_windrun_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 100/100/100/100</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/XlNv2uF4l_k?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lyralei enchants gusts of winds to fight incoming attacks.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Windranger</Owner><Name>Focus Fire</Name><Description>Windranger channels the wind to gain 500 additional attack speed against a single enemy unit or structure, though with a reduction to her attack damage.  Extra damage from secondary item effects is not reduced.  Lasts 20 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/windrunner_focusfire_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/100/125</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/jj7cWGyhj2o?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Lyralei's ability to bombard opponents with a flurry of arrows is unparalleled - even at the expense of accuracy.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Winter Wyvern</Owner><Name>Arctic Burn</Name><Description>Winter Wyvern soars upon an arctic wind, granting her unobstructed movement and allowing her to exhale a blistering chill into each attack. While soaring, her attacks travel further and faster, and slow enemies with a magical freeze that strips them of 8% of their current health each second. Her sight is also hardened against night's chill, granting her 400 additional vision range at night while soaring.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/winter_wyvern_arctic_burn_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/110/100/90</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 50/40/30/20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/QJjASKaV5pM?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The same organ where some dragons stoke their inner flame is, in Auroth, a crucible of unimaginable cold. From deep within her frosty gullet, an exhalation sends enemies into burning agony.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Winter Wyvern</Owner><Name>Splinter Blast</Name><Description>Launches a ball of brittle ice toward an enemy. The ice shatters on impact, leaving the primary target completely unaffected, while hurling damaging splinters into nearby enemies in a 500 radius. Enemies struck by these splinters are slowed by 25%.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/winter_wyvern_splinter_blast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 120/130/140/150</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 7</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/SCGete8RbbU?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Produced slowly by specialized vesicles in her frozen gullet, Winter Wyvern blast shards of ice at her enemies.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Winter Wyvern</Owner><Name>Cold Embrace</Name><Description>Encases an ally in an icy cocoon, freezing them solid while healing a base amount as well as a percentage of their maximum health each second. The cocoon blocks all physical damage.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/winter_wyvern_cold_embrace_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/75/75/75</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 24/21/18/15</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/8UDmKdYAQP4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>From winter's heart comes a cold, healing embrace. The ice slows the blood and allows the spell to better work its curative magic.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Winter Wyvern</Owner><Name>Winter's Curse</Name><Description>Winter Wyvern freezes an enemy in place while striking those nearby with a maddening curse which causes them to attack their frozen ally with increased attack speed. The frozen ally and those cursed to attack their ally are immune to all damage from their enemies.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/winter_wyvern_winters_curse_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 250</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/AW7PdQw92ak?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The oldest of the bookwurm’s spells, this curse lends truth to the old saw: sometimes the enemy of my enemy is my enemy still.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Witch Doctor</Owner><Name>Paralyzing Cask</Name><Description>Launches a cask of paralyzing powder that ricochets between enemy units, stunning and damaging those it hits.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/witch_doctor_paralyzing_cask_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 110/120/130/140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20/18/16/14</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/GcM3eChjrms?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Witch Doctor recycles the bones of fallen friends and foes, using the powder as part of his arsenal of charms and alchemy.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Witch Doctor</Owner><Name>Voodoo Restoration</Name><Description>Witch Doctor focuses his magic to heal nearby allied units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/witch_doctor_voodoo_restoration_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 20/30/40/50</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 0</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/yBY5jmY0iR4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Zharvakko's hocus pocus is not limited only to hexxing his opponents and is quite adept at curing ailments.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Witch Doctor</Owner><Name>Maledict</Name><Description>Curses all enemy Heroes in a small area, causing them to take a set amount of damage each second, as well as bursts of damage every 4 seconds based on how much health they have lost since the curse began.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/witch_doctor_maledict_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 105/110/115/120</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 20</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/9upNFFHTnPA?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Certain voodoo magics can make an enemy regret engaging the Witch Doctor.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Witch Doctor</Owner><Name>Death Ward</Name><Description>CHANNELED - Summons a deadly ward to attack enemy heroes within 700 range. Lasts a maximum of 8 seconds.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/witch_doctor_death_ward_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 200/200/200</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 80</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/tEl6x3-pYuc?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Witch Doctor performs a ritualistic dance, one that haunts the dreams of those who live to recount it.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Wraith King</Owner><Name>Wraithfire Blast</Name><Description>Wraith King sears an enemy unit with spectral fire, dealing damage and stunning, then dealing damage over time and slowing the target.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skeleton_king_hellfire_blast_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 140</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 8</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/cjBrHQKjxm4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Ostarion calls on his damned lineage, laying waste to his opponents.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Wraith King</Owner><Name>Vampiric Aura</Name><Description>Nearby friendly units restore health based on the damage they deal when attacking enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skeleton_king_vampiric_aura_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/0ZD6iTDTjcQ?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Wraith King's blade drains his enemy's essence to feed his aura.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Wraith King</Owner><Name>Mortal Strike</Name><Description>Wraith King passively gains a chance to deal bonus damage on an attack.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skeleton_king_mortal_strike_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/UMPnfE_N0YI?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>One blow to crush a foe.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Wraith King</Owner><Name>Reincarnation</Name><Description>Wraith King's form regroups after death, allowing him to resurrect when killed in battle.  Upon death, enemy units in a 900 radius will be slowed.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/skeleton_king_reincarnation_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 160</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 260/160/60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/3yGidbPrewk?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Conspirators against the Wraith King wonder why he never stays dead.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Zeus</Owner><Name>Arc Lightning</Name><Description>Hurls a bolt of lightning that leaps through nearby enemy units.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/zuus_arc_lightning_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 65/70/75/80</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 1.60</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/uHcb8gCUP3s?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>Arc Lightning is Zeus' favorite spell to use against puny mortals.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Zeus</Owner><Name>Lightning Bolt</Name><Description>Calls down a bolt of lightning to strike an enemy unit, causing damage and a mini-stun. When cast, Lightning Bolt briefly provides unobstructed vision and True Sight around the target in a 750 radius. Can be cast on the ground, affecting the closest enemy hero in 325 range.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/zuus_lightning_bolt_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 75/95/115/135</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 6</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/S5xDQfHBSw4?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>A shocking punishment for rebellious heathen.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Zeus</Owner><Name>Static Field</Name><Description>Zeus shocks all nearby enemy units whenever he casts a spell, causing damage proportional to their current health.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/zuus_static_field_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana /><Cooldown /><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/mZm0z2mlPvY?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The air crackles with static when the Thundergod walks the world.</Lore></Skill><Skill><Owner>Zeus</Owner><Name>Thundergod's Wrath</Name><Description>Strikes all enemy heroes with a bolt of lightning, no matter where they may be.  Thundergod's Wrath also provides True Sight around each hero struck.  If an enemy hero is invisible, it takes no damage, but the True Sight is still created at that hero's location.

Upgradable by Aghanim's Scepter.</Description><Image>http://cdn.dota2.com/apps/dota2/images/abilities/zuus_thundergods_wrath_hp2.png?v=3581466</Image><Mana> Mana Cost: 225/325/450</Mana><Cooldown> Cooldown: 90</Cooldown><Video>http://www.youtube.com/embed/IGhJdGh8CH8?hd=1&amp;rel=0</Video><Lore>The Lord of Heaven smites all who oppose him, near or far.</Lore></Skill></Skills>